[music]
the situation
All
[music]
Chaos was born from the union of earth and sky
Of pearl. The Almighty divided him into two parts.
I divided it into. Celestial energy becomes spiritual
The pearl and demonic energy became the demon sphere.
Heaven cursed that exactly three years later
The demon ball is destroyed by lightning
Will go. But due to the intervention of Shengon Pau
Bakut Gola Chenchang near Leasing
Born as the third son Nija.
On the other hand, the Spiritual Pearl is also known as Obing.
He became the third son of Lungraj. but luckily
Both of them became very close friends.
Because of the values ​​given by your parents
Nesa gave up her demonic tendencies and went to Chatan
protected the pass and together with these reached heaven
Facing the wrath of
Changed his destiny.
[music]
[Appreciation]
he faced the wrath
But their bodies were destroyed and without bodies
that their souls may perish very soon
Will go. The sacred lotus protects the souls and
It nourishes. Now I can use it to
I am the creator of the physical body.
[music]
Come on start.
[Appreciation]
Something is wrong. but your body
The lotus root is very important for this. have you
Did you wipe your dirty laundry soap with your finger? O!
Do not panic. There is mud on my feet. wash
It will be cleared from. I don't care about that
Would have fallen. did you clean your nose with that same finger
of Hey this is just lotus powder and
Nothing. Look, it's just powder.
Look, it's ready.
This will save your life and your
The soul too. Oh, there won't be a chance like this again soon
will get.
Hey, die.
[music]
Sir what is it
Is? What is this? no i have been doing this for so long
looking for
Was. There is no break for the memory of
There is no art of looking for it
Joint. Ho ho ho, may my evil eye not fall on you.
Thanks Bailey. Hey don't move too much now
It is under construction.
Master Tai, I just met Shagong Bao and
Troops to protect Shuttle Pass from Lungs
I have prepared it. Do not panic. lungs of hell
are monitoring the demons so that no one
I couldn’t escape from here. from Shangon Bau alone
We are not afraid at all. Let the profession in front of you
This is my service. A unique sight.
Did he think the idea was mine? But the old
Why did you give it a form? Give it a new look.
Absolutely. Parents always take care of their children
I only wish well. we are tall and strong
Make it. And you too are extremely defeated. strengthen the man
And it should be great. Another smart one too.
He should also be sweet and innocent. Oho
Decide it. how do you want to see yourself
yes? Tall and powerful. Hey shut up Harasmi.
Be the son of the strong and great Joseph.
What is this? He is saying make it yourself.
I should have done this work earlier.
His time will keep passing. Come on Sarah
The focus should be on you because you are the water
If it is made of elements then it should be anointed with water also
Needed
[music]
opened
[Appreciation]
[music]
Let no one cast an evil eye on you, this is yours
What do you think, it's done.
I think this one is really cool.
But it will take a lot of time to make it completely.
Should I keep the previous one till then? We first
The one that will be right. We are right from the first one
Is.
We
If you are made of fire elements then your
We adorn ourselves with fire only.
[music]
The commander may have seen an enemy in the sea.
Is Sen Gau the only one who has the army with him?
Master you have come alone, you are doing your work
Please come and sit so that we can see Gurudev
Tai I will also have to go with them, be careful
Your body is still under construction
[music]
Shagomba, tell me why have you come here?
When you find out I'm with Lux
what am I going to do together so I thought to myself
I will just go. Commander of the mine at Chattang Pass
The army is present. Master Tai is also our friend
Are. You are alone here, nothing to us
You will be able to spoil it.
Well who said I came here alone?
If they knew about the Spiritual Pearl
walked. So avenge your son's death. One
All the Eastern peoples had their own empire
I will file charges. When this comes out, mother
Throw you in public amongst your peers
will be given and it is not good for you
will be. People sit in the palace and worship their son
How will you be able to take the badma? I am worried about you
It has been happening.
[music]
There is no need to be so happy, idiots.
I wanted to help, but it seemed like
It’s that you don’t appreciate it.
[music]
Maybe you forgot what I can do.
Do you know
it is called a sky-tearing nail
Shengong Bao is taking this nail of mine with him
The leg will come near and then I will tear apart the sky
will return it. then the tensions of hell
I will destroy your enemies completely.
[music]
[Appreciation]
demon of hell
How can this be? for thousands of years
He was imprisoned in the netherworld. But how are they liars?
You have agreed to come. Tied up in chains
Because of this we did not even run away from here
will find it. This is a profitable deal for you.
what do you say brother? you your brother's
Benefit
You will think about it. Talk about the issue. What do you want
You?
In this hellfire that burns the skin
Every moment feels like centuries. If you are using this
Reduce the heat of the lava a little
If you give, we will help you with all our might
do.
Uday what is this Goombaun going to do?
these brother brother
[music]
Don't leave us. Now, we will tell the commander
What will you answer? It's good that someone told us
Didn't see it. Yellow. what is this for? you are mine
Break the leg. I break your hand.
They will say that Yaksha has done it. When the commander us
If he sees someone injured, he won't say anything, right?
hit softly or hit hard
Oye
you stopped short
People beat Gurudev is here now
He drove them all away so don't lie
It was all your doing so what did I do
How naive are you
O Baba, take these two away from this idiot
I have been caught in a fight, come here first, Fakir
[music]
No one could survive.
[Appreciation]
[music]
Obiang is still alive. Shan between bass and gluten
War makes no sense. To Tai Obing
Preparing the body.
Liars
I will not say it. energy
No shield
Gurudev
Gurudev, come here Gurudev, Tai, give me a new body
is giving. Stop this war. Listen
Shang saved your disciple. Thank you
Grandfather. Oh then Neja will also be somewhere around here.
Oh my god stop it Gurudev they have to die
It will happen.
Did you think you'd break the energy shield? own
Seem black to me.
[music]
No
[Appreciation]
This energy
[music]
father
Father, I failed to save my people
Don't think about all this. I want you to
Stay safe. This is enough for me.
You just stay with me.
[music]
Open up.
Your body speaks to you. These
He has just been born. I can't bear all that
Can.
Hey, you are still raw. Oh what happened?
why don't you understand that your body is still raw
Is. If you exert too much force then this body too
It will become useless like OB. hey understand oh
Fatty come quickly for being another body
get ready. After making two consecutive bodies
Kamal has run out of energy. without body
Otherwise the soul will be destroyed. do something
Gurudev. without the sacred lotus hey mamma
I can't do anything. Something
No. Maybe I was not worthy of this sir.
if my sacrifice would give you life
If so, I have no objection to it. Shame
Do it and keep quiet. I am happy to be a daalu gola
and you are talking about dying.
Dad just takes pity on you
Do it. We have to stop all this.
This is my last wish.
[music]
There must be some way, there must be some way.
Try and do something quickly. one and the same
is the way. put opine into your body
Have to stay. two souls are not in one body
It can stay. This puts both lives at risk
Is. Spiritual Granddaughter and Dana Gola are the same source
If it comes out then I don't think there is any problem
Should not happen. oh come inside me now
Quick.
It comes.
[Appreciation]
It feels very strange. Obing is that you?
I am inside. I love you from inside
The sound is being heard. This is going to be fun.
This solution is only for seven days.
But what will happen after that? of Yashu Palace
There is a medicine lying in the safe. Sanjeevani
Booty Immortal who returned the power of magical things
Can. If we have it, it is holy
The lotus will bloom again.
But how will we get that medicine?
I will pray to the almighty. somewhere like this
So you are not complaining about me and my lungs
will you do it. I don't think so Almighty Lungs
will save the son of. if they don't save
Then you yourself will not be able to save yourself. Yushu Palace
Situated between sect. whose guard
For all my sons to attack even heaven
If needed I will do it. Maharaj, calm down.
I have a plan. the disciple of the moon
They are the first ones to move forward
One gets a chance to take a trial. which this
Not only do they pass the trial
Immortality is gained from Yushu's treasure chest
They also have the right to take any magical item
It is available. So you mean that medicine
Neja took part in that trial to bring
Take. Na Na Neza Suri is full of power.
He will be caught as soon as he reaches there. and also so
Neja's body has his divinity in it, right?
will hide the energy of.
If he passes the trial there then no
Only he will get that medicine along with
He will become immortal, this does not mean anything
This will save both Aubing and Neza
All will go well that ends well in my opinion
This is not correct, if there is another way then tell me
Learn to walk on the right path of the almighty
Have faith in justice and see my wife and
I myself will beg for mercy that our
Our child should not be punished for his deeds.
You mortals only have a few decades
is experiencing. Give me a speech on immortality
Wale who are you?
As far as I can remember, I have been
I am alive and I can tell you a truth
I want to give it. if my son dies
With him this war pass will turn into ashes again.
stop
Go. He is my friend now and I am here for him
I will do anything. but something happened to Chint Pas
So no one in the world knows the name of Lung Mehar
He will not know.
[music]
So from now on, no one except Neha and Tai
Will not go beyond the limits of Chatang. Seven
I did not receive the medicine within a few days.
When the news of my sect went out, Chatang
The pass will remain submerged forever. Me
I don't trust my siblings, nor do I
I can stay outside the body for longer periods.
The future of Objern Pass is in your hands
that it is better than the power of silence
The message can be delivered.
Commander ji, we want to say goodbye to Prince Neja
Have come. to save the whole city
To say thank you to them. you are very
They are good. My son has been here for years
Only caused damage. I always know
Yuvraj was born to do something great
Has happened. Just look at this huge forehead,
Beautiful face, long nose, full cheeks and
Thick lips are a must have for a great personality
all the things. I told you whatever I saw.
Prince, make sure you brush your teeth after eating.
Would you know the name of Yuvraj's Bakhsh gang?
Gang. Every member will follow your orders.
Yuvraj, do you want to record it like this?
for me. Prince, you are now three years old
and I don't have any girlfriend yet.
Has interest in music. we'll play something
Are.
[music]
Who do I want to play with?
What happened? You will enjoy it. Will anyone play?
I will play. you are always with me shuttle
Wanted to play [ __ ], right? Listen to his hand
It's kinda like that.
And I am a warrior.
Papa Warrior's child what's the matter? Any
No matter. We will play it again sometime. what is this
Hui? When you are having this much fun then never again
Why? I am alright! I am fine I also come
Am. What if the Queen gets hurt? why less me
Are you understanding? I have also fought many wars.
Neja catch it.
Hey son why didn't you catch it? If only
I wouldn't be a demon sphere. what did you say?
Nothing. It's time to leave. from leaving
Didn't Neza hug his mother first?
Will you apply it?
No mother. people watching.
Bye. Wait a minute.
There is food for you and Gurudev in this
The stuff is there. Not hungry. Yes, okay. Correct
Is. Let's go Begum. wait. I bought a ticket too
Is.
Your body is still immature so put more pressure on it
Don't apply it. Yes, okay. on your anger
To keep control. Go there and stay calm. Now
You have to struggle on your own without me and your father
You have to learn to handle it.
Oh, if the innocent children would hug their mother
So what would have happened? limit reached. forever
I am going for a while. Let's go now
[music]
What happened? Isn't it tasty? Eat
Do you only know how to eat? Look at me.
There is some concern about the trial
thought.
What will happen in this trial? your sadhana
will take the exam of. in front of these two
He ate grains of the earth like three grains
The kings must be defeated. You want to fight, right? In this
So, I am an expert. but your last
The secret will be revealed through power. So come to Bin
Let my body be burnt. His divine energy
Very powerful. It's easy to say. see
Are.
No sir, loosen your body. Now let's go
Obin hold your body and face me.
What are you doing Obin? When one soul becomes another
resides in the body and its will power
If the owner of the body is no more than the soul
You can't run it according to your wishes.
[music]
Stop for once. the more you hold him
Oh it will be just as difficult.
Use Tangu Money.
[music]
Don't worry I'm coming to help you.
[Laughter]
Are we about to reach Yushu Palace.
Just look at yourself. how will you do it? If
If this situation persists then I will not eat at all
will get. The body is big but the friend has come yes
Guruji.
I have sleep cords. ton now this
What is? Eat one. You will fall asleep immediately.
As you sleep, Obing is completely yours
He will gain control over his body. Wonderful.
Hey, I have to eat only one. so I was already telling you
No.
Keep it up.
[music]
Gurudev! The real fun is about to begin now. Any
What's wrong? Don't worry. It is visible
Nija's body is completely under your control
Is. do it again
Are. This time I will not show any mercy.
So fight with all your strength.
[music]
Sorry, I applied too much force. Good
So it was. He faced me with empty hands.
Gurudev from your nose
If the blood heat is a bit too much then drink water
don't say anything
Pushana reached Kullu mountain. I heard
Here one day is equal to a year. Worry
Do not do it. This is not heaven. But so many
People have all come here to become immortal. Moon
The sect is famous all over the world. every
Somebody wants to get in on this. Just look at this
The ring of the immortal soul of the Moon Sect
Sign. Because of this you get respect everywhere
Will get respect. U serious. Your
Both brothers have been successful in the trial.
Meaning brother of Ne, both brothers are counted
He is among the top disciples of the sect.
You already know. Nessa is very naughty.
So to bring him on the right path I
I always give the example of his brothers.
Maybe you don't know your brothers
Wants to become.
[music]
You are lucky to be the son of the famous demon
You are meeting the hunters. of the demons
These hunters roam the earth and
Hunting the demon that plagues humanity
Let's do it so that peace can prevail. Predators
The immortal soul that leads the
He is a disciple. Is he a descendant of Shet?
Is.
[music]
Gurudev, how is the smoke there? that yushu palace
is the most valuable treasure of. Tayanak Kund.
Master Tai we are back after a long time
I met Puliyan brother, I have heard about Gurudev
You take care of the palace while being in Samadhi
I am here to test my immortality
I have brought my disciple with me Neja Gurudev
Pay your respects to Ulian, Gurudev Fulian
So you are a reincarnation of a Spiritual Pearl
Oh wow that's great very nice
awesome awesome. I hope the almighty blesses you
You will not disappoint me. To live up to expectations.
Just look at this. Its energy is very noble
And powerful
Is. I have worked very hard on his brain these days
condition is not good
Is. What are you doing? this is not pee this
The show is the palace. It hit very hard. Village G
Take this child to the toilet. Toilet me
Don't think. You have to turn around, idiot. go to sleep.
Toilet means a place to relieve oneself.
Its actions are wrong but it is as per the understanding
Not there.
wow so much
white wow wow wow wow
awesome wow
White: Does this entire palace belong to the brother-in-law? This much
Where does one get the money to buy Sarah Jade?
The Yu in Yushu means jade, right? So Shu
what would that mean? Maybe humility is a crime
Or
void? Is the toilet also made by brother-in-law?
Do we souls also feel the need to pee?
By the way, would Gurudev make pot of value?
Are? This is a place of meditation. Voice is low.
How far is this toilet? not have control
remained. Listen, sister.
This happened by mistake. clothes me
Have to change. Go ahead yourself. but to me
So I don't know about the toilet. by corridor
Right hand then left.
[music]
Wow how wonderful it is. What is the matter. Wow.
Did I go astray? where are you going
I felt lost. Follow me.
You did a good job by growing your spiritual pearl
Kia Tai this is a big deal for the sect.
It's not like that. All this is Gurudev's
I am grateful to you. This dew of Kulun is a very rare medicine
Is. It usually takes six months to fill a vessel.
It takes months. But today it was full.
Looks like you have very good luck.
Tai Almighty seems pleased with you.
what are you doing and didn't you drink water properly
go. this is good but what you are thinking is
It is not like that. Not there.
I have urinated in this.
My Gurudev is a little clumsy. Let go. Sorry
Tax. Brother, time is very valuable. Why
Nor should Neja be sent directly for examination.
What's the hurry? drink a couple of glasses
Take. No more and no more. Ah okay then its okay.
My disciple Dir will oversee this. Donations
The next victim of the hunters is named after him
We give it. Haste Brother
This is too much, my brother is always in a hurry
Is. This year the dew tastes different
Is. It is quite delicious. same way again
Should be put to use. yes gurudev.
[music]
Why did you stop? I've been throwing it for the whole six hours
He is Gurusen. It won’t be possible now. Idiot
There is no laziness in sadhana. My command
No one will stop without it.
Commander Lising of Chatang Pass has come.
Shengba was very close to Chatang Pass in the battle of yesterday
Soldiers were injured and now there is a shortage of medicines
Has occurred. I request you for the doctors
the way should be opened so that the necessary
Could not get medicines.
I request you then who threw this to you?
Gamme Haramkhor
wait wait wait wait
[Appreciation]
Wait, take the one you caught first
Come. He ran away during the war.
Commander, please take it back.
Gurudev Sen, am I making a mistake? I too am one
I am a demon. prove his son innocent
I had caught Yaksha to do this. Now
Because everything went well and nothing went wrong
If it hasn't even worked then let it go.
Of course I'm just a simpleton
I am a pawn. Maybe you are not understanding. Any
I will not go from here. Humans are far away
Is. No demons either. I say my thing
Listen, Master Shan. Have mercy on me. I
I am also a demon. We are both villains.
No, I am not a typical villain. Who
Atmik knows the secret of Modi, he can read it here
Have to stay. At the moment it is essential that we
Healing the wounds of the injured
Apply it. I request you
Is. Save his life.
Guruji, we have caught a spy that boy
Came from out of town. it attacked us
Also did it. So make this also as panti.
brother brother is this you? this is it brother
I am.
Shahanshaba
If you haven't come home for ages, I miss you
Was being. what are you doing here? father
has been sent to look for you. See your di
Compost is telling me where are you?
How is his dad? He is fine. that's ok
Is. Ever since you entered the Yusho Palace
Father's courage has increased. like the seventh
You are in the sky You are the only one in our village
have been able to achieve the status of immortal soul and
Demons come from far and wide to learn from dad.
By the way, why have you come here? you to me
I promised you that when I learn to be a human being
I will go. You will call me to Youshu Palace. See
I learned it.
For so many years, I have been working hard every day.
Did not rest even for a day. you are mine
Brother, he is an inspiration. For the greatness of Yushu
My brother roams the world on the orders of heaven
Taxes are providing justice.
By the way brother what are you doing here? They
Do you do all this work alone? You
Why is the Chandang bus surrounded? that is real
This is the thing. Master Shen Chatang Pass
are protecting the . Yes. evil powers
When the city was attacked, Master Shen and
The Sea Sect helped us. Our
On behalf of the people, Master Shen is heartily
Thanks
Was. No praise needed. wow bro now
So that's awesome. Was this the one who attacked Chatang Pass?
Did?
You are a blot on the name of the demon. feel ashamed
Needed good shahba
She wants to go to Yushu Palace for a few more years
Will you wait? Yes but why? I am now a human
I can become one. The thing is I have 12 goldfish
I am getting ready to go into the souls.
12 Golden Immortal Souls? once this work is done
Let's go then, we will go. Ok.
No problem brother. Progress is necessary. I
I can go to Yushu Palace any time. And
I'm still raw in becoming a human being anyway
Am. A little more practice is needed.
I brought this for you from Shahbhaav Mahal
Was. What is this? Is. Yashu Mahal people have their own
Gives the disciple the pills of immortality. One
The pill gives the fruits of 10 years of sadhana.
But this is very precious brother and yours
This will be useful for your progress, right? Me
I don't like their taste. With my hard work I
I want to move forward. you take these
And distribute it among the family. No. No,
Dad will scold me. Well done, brother
Do not put it aside. Take these pills and go away.
This is a battlefield. if you'll stay here
Then my attention will be diverted. Then
I walk
[music]
Am. Brother, you have to reach 12 immortal souls
only
will be. I will continue working hard.
Thanks for the help. But I'm someone
Can't let him go out. This is a yagya. Take
Take this back too. no i am not yours
I was helping that kid because the truth
And children learn humanity at this age.
Are.
stop
Go. Give me a list of medicines.
[Appreciation]
I am Neja, the third and only prince.
Although I am a stupid sir, I am death for both of them.
Today I am keeping that land a secret from both of you.
I will get it for you. stay away from me because I
yes neja.
Leave the gluttonous bowl. Now death will come to you, puppy
to give.
You have to set foot on the mountain of robbers
How dare the idiot? you are so
Leader, come, come. I will give you some fun.
You are using impudent language. Khawa Hajj Food
Leave it, use your hands.
[music]
[Appreciation]
come on come
You go. no no bakhuda in our hands
This royal voice is not in the morning. from the child
It is a shame for me to fight. What do you mean
Go
Listen, this is your age to get trained
and I'm stressed with the kids anyway
I do not force. Yes. What happened?
Why did you go again? I don't know my
My sleep is light. Maybe it opened with these rods.
oh my god it seems the pills are having an effect
It stopped. And I eat three or four. If
If you don't get it, you will get hurt
Is. Was about to stop. Pardon me. I felt
bye o go
Is. You turned out to be weak. Master Tai maybe
The exam should be stopped. This a little more
Have to work hard. It has come, it is very fast. These
So he is playing with the doors. actually weak
Pretending to be. Pills Pills
I need pills. I already did
I had given you a slit. So, I will call you and see you. thick on
Is. Should I give these pills in the soup? So
I will drink this soup.
You're stealing our royal soup. Now
what is yours? I look at my glory.
[music]
It tastes very bad. Look at my dhobi paan
Son, tell me where are you pretending? Hey Fight
It had not started.
[Appreciation]
The fight is also over.
[music]
Arrogance cannot be digested. Whatever it be it
I will crush it in the scarf. you wore a suit
Why did you put it? God face so useless
I couldn't digest it. Look darling
This is also a drama. If you have to, take the bullet
It will be needed.
Dheer is watching. I won't give you a bullet
Can. What should I do? What should I do? Something
No. I have another way too. somewhere
what do you mean? Now both of them have to drink vomit
Will need it. But that would make her vomit again.
What's the big deal? I also have the snake of the Yaksha
So I had to go. It is said that without pain
does not get success. Nija same fate
can defeat the . my parents and friends
's life is in danger. and people nearby
Now the leader will beat you to death.
[music]
Just by looking at what's trapped inside of me. I
I will change my fate.
[music]
I've already told you I look like this, but
It is full of strength. Mastai first leader
Save the. More about Secretary Booty later
I will think about it. This cannot happen. Back
Will fight. Back
Will fight. He acts. this is it
It's a good thing no everyone fainted. Yours
have a royal coup
Went. We'll take revenge with curved punches
From. Ready
[music]
It is important to catch everyone if even one is left behind
It will cause trouble to people. All of them are in Yash Mahal
Take it. Sects are a bad way to go
He will teach you to leave the world and walk on the right path.
What happened to his face? nothing something
No. Faces keep changing from time to time.
The spiritual granddaughter is not like an ordinary person.
Hey, don't be so cautious next time. hey you
So I took mine out.
[music]
Hey who is this kid? There is intelligence and maybe
Moses' younger brother and Moti's reincarnation
It is sent by the Almighty.
[Appreciation]
He doesn't look like a prince. hunched back,
Stray gait. girl with hair bent down
Eyes and black spots. looks just like a ghost
Used tobe.
Hey, don't do this at all. Thai
[music]
Tai what do the movements of the stars say today? Six
The six stars of Brother meet once a decade
Are. When these six stars come in a row
So sound and pictures from Jeth's Spotium
can be sent thousands of miles and
Our brothers can gather together. today the same
It's time for all the golden immortal souls to
There will be a meeting. I am still among immortal souls
If I don't join in, I shouldn't come.
That time is not far. no no this
Is not right. I really can't do this.
Then why are you sitting up there? shut up
running from guru
Is. Water was poured and smoke came out.
[music]
Welcome immortal souls. hello.
Meet the newest member of our family. this is it
Brother Tai. These are based on the hopes of the almighty
In the rebirth of the Spiritual Pearl by standing true
have proven to be helpful.
Just bend over.
You know that religious war will happen then
Today we will first talk about its preparation
do. If the Chand sect has tied the tradition
We will win. Recently lived sects
has also made a lot of progress. make us smarter
Have to stay.
Yes, there is a sect with fur and lions
animals gather and living beings and fibers and
Are born from eggs. this war of ours
It is a war for the existence of the community. Us
We have to be careful and make it stronger
Will have to try my best. Correct!
Said. That's why I started preparing
Done. Pills of immortality. of quality
According to this, about 9000 bullets can be stored.
Are. I believe that this will increase our powers
Will go. But where did these pills come from? Own
Gurudev put his sadhana at stake
Working hard together with Tahiayan Kund
These pills have been prepared. Brother, he told us
Have done a lot of work for the sect. Their
Should be praised.
Yes, apart from this sect there are other powers too.
who is conspiring. from the immortal soul
When the conspirators are discovered, the demons
The hunters will be dispatched. Mostly
We are not in any danger from demons. Only
Except for one demon. Oh and who is that?
Longs of the Eastern Sea.
What is this joke? they have already gone to heaven
had surrendered before. we on someone
Can't trust it. According to me their
Surrender is nothing but a deception.
What is Lons' crime, after all? He so
Demons were imprisoned in the netherworld for thousands of years
kept. But they have a lot of power. If
They betrayed us in the war
The whole game can change.
Can't do it. of our religion and justice
The reputation is renowned in the world. if we
If you attack people who have surrendered then
Then tell me how will the world trust us?
That's correct. A decision has to be taken after careful consideration.
But it's been a long time. The immortal souls have
I said it. Now why doubt this? Yes
The time for the confluence of stars is about to end
And now there is no issue to talk about. So
We conclude this meeting. Brother Bullion,
Jinjha and Mojha are mine and brother Pushiyan's
There are disciples. He is away from home for many years
I have been doing sadhana since. and he his younger brother
Never met him. because the stars
There is still some time left in the confluence. Why
No, during this time I got these brothers to meet.
Should I give it? Our offer is very good.
[music]
Oh my god, I am in trouble. What should I do now?
Why? What happened? Just look at me. First
This meeting is going to be useless. As such
It won't happen at all. Really? Because
Your willpower is very strong. stature
He is small but has a big heart. you are lucky
But you are very noble from inside. Under the eyes
has black spots, flat nose and bad teeth
but I think you're awesome.
And your brother will definitely think the same.
Thanks for compliment.
What are you doing? In my place you are mine
Meet the brothers. no no I I this
How can I do it? No Neza
No, the boy is a little shy.
yes bro
[music]
o are you crying? yes i love my brothers
I remembered it. do you also have a brother? We
Brother
Were. I also had two lovely brothers. you lucky
You are going to. so what are you talking about now
Were you there? They were saying that they were sad that so many
I haven't heard from you for years and
They
Asked how is everything at home? your parents
Ok? what do you do? and your
who is my friend? It is also said that if the future
If you have any problem with us
Please tell me. don't forget that you have two brothers
Are. Who will always stand with you.
yes, what happened to you? Nothing. to us
The garbage is gone too.
Is it possible that you have become emotional? Silent
Stay. I told you it is garbage. ok as it is
You
Say. I don't want to talk.
Ok, good. I remain silent.
Yes, you are angry right now. Nija Nisha. Come on.
Yes. I have been very angry since childhood.
Mom and dad worry about me the whole day.
Although your father crossed the Chatang Pass
I attacked you but I know all about it
They did it just for you. And
Today I told my brothers also to stand for me
Worried
saw. Our family made many sacrifices.
You are a monster and I am a demon. both of us
He is a burden on his family.
But I added a little of it as per my wish
But now further decisions will be taken as per my wish.
You get well soon. then a place among immortal souls
We will make it so that no one is troubled. yes and we
People can get respect only by becoming immortal souls
Are. ok promise. I am an immortal soul
I will stay.
[music]
Progress can only be made with determination and hard work
It can. at this rate it will take hundreds of years
will become useless. Talk about rituals
So those should be our priorities. Life
Strength, energy and spirit. if you think
it is difficult because
You were born a demon. only by exerting force
You can change your fate and become immortal
You can become a soul.
I am not afraid of life and death. I
I have come to challenge the authority. My
It's my luck. I am not indebted to anyone. These
A bad boy will become immortal someday.
Well done. In how few words you have
I have said inspirational things. the poem was
Fabulous. You all should learn from this kid.
Needed
Was it really that good? I just now
Made it. It was very nice. There's passion in every word
Was. This was a poem in which you
The purpose is revealed. your friend
The future is very bright. Hey, stop it.
I agree that it is good, but it is still nothing.
None, there are many shortcomings. your eyes
Why are there black spots under the hair? Seems like
You always stay awake at night. Your
There is lack of discipline in life. with food
You should focus on yourself. Otherwise
You will not be able to become our soul. These
The black spots are there from birth. just by saying
The heart is revealed. look at yourself in the mirror
Son. Useless, careless, and messy. You
If I had disciples, they would have regained the human body
Teaches me to make it. What can you do? so I
I can't become handsome. listen to me
Please teach me. Calm down. you are the Guru's
You have gone out in search. Listen kid, I can see it.
Your purpose is very big. to you
I accept you as my disciple. Jai ho Gurudev
of.
Come work hard with your brothers. How
Hard work? To become immortal. not all of this
I will increase it. Just want to be handsome. Nonsense.
You are combining sadhana with beauty. Decision
do what you want? will you teach me or
Should I go? From now on we are no longer teacher and student
are. Life is like these button eyes
Cut. That's ok. I simply wanted that to
You should agree with love. What? threatened me.
Three is enough. go back where you came from
Children. if you disrupt my class
So it will not be good for your health.
Sorry.
[music]
You failed.
very nice. I did not give you eyes
Gave. Yellow.
[Appreciation]
[music]
This was the base. Did you see one?
There is no problem between us. it would be better
Go. I can't lose.
[music]
Otherwise, friends, you are not my yoga
what do you want to do don't leave it
knock down
one minute you
So you realized that your speed is too high
Not there. I just turned off the power
No one can defeat me in the distance of water.
[music]
Do you know how to make ice?
[Appreciation]
keep calm if you exert yourself then your body will become useless
Now what will we do if the electricity goes out
does not cross
loose sea clouds sky the wind passes beneath me
The clouds will burst and it will rain heavily
[music]
father
Oh my God, please end this rain magic.
[music]
Now you will not survive.
I didn't want to take your life then
Why did you sacrifice your hand? All the students were attentive
Listen. Take these demons to the palace now.
Yes.
wait put them down put all the pickles down
Are you a member of some cult?
yes you recognized it correctly
So these are all the immortal souls of the Yushu Palace.
Don't misbehave. Entering the Yushu Palace
And learn to walk on the right path
There is nothing wrong in it. you all right now
Put down your weapons.
[music]
Dad, how did you come back?
Don't do this.
[music]
[Appreciation]
yours so much
Courage
[music]
no dad
river Neza turned into ice
[music]
Two. You can't run away.
[Appreciation]
[music]
daddy go away
Run
Daddy won't survive
Move from the front. He was just saving his father
And you want to kill him.
[music]
[Appreciation]
Elephant nails, bird eyelashes, chicken
feathers of, boar's hair, Lung's blood. One
basket and put. Mukhi flower, wild cardamom,
Dried ginger, seaweed, datura seeds.
Commander ji, whatever items were written in the list
I got Sara. along with marine items
There are also 100 baskets. We also have food
There was some shortage, right?
Master Shen, stop. we have prepared the food
Did. We would love it if you would stay.
You all Commander Lee kindness. They
I was hired here. I think it's a demon
Is. But he is very kind at heart. As long as this
As long as no one makes a mistake it is ours
There is responsibility.
Did you like the food here? No.
Not that bad. So take some more and
Take this wine also. Due to sadhana, I
I have stopped drinking alcohol for years. Soul
only by renouncing the desires of purity
It will be. Master Shen also says that
The soul is purified by good deeds.
Saying something doesn't help. I reach there
I have reached a point from where there is no return. excuse me
But the truth cannot be hidden for long. Any
Someday the truth would have been revealed to everyone
Is. If you keep ruining the lives of innocent people
I will keep taking it. You won't admit your mistakes
So you can lie to the world. But
How can you stop yourself from lying? Is such
Is sadhana done? Because sadhana is good
By following the path of deeds and truth
I don't want to listen to your nonsense. You
Don't know anything about sadhana.
Brother
Who did this to you? Enemies
did
Gave.
dad dad's hand
He cut it off. Tell me who did it?
his name is
Nee
[music]
Congratulations on passing level 2. Brother
Send the news to me. Gurudev now have some pills
Busy making it. not out yet
Have come out. before the next step you
Why don't you take a rest day? We have
Only two days are left. No no I am totally
I am fine. Please continue. like yours
Desire. This is your last exam. skull
Sheeshji, the demon queen of the mountain.
Someone wants to meet Master Tai right now.
Please help us. About time pass.
Something has happened.
[music]
Father
Mother
papa mother
[music]
[Appreciation]
Baba Mother
[music]
calm down calm down let go quickly
Don't
[music]
As soon as I came out of the meditation, I got this news
Who can commit such a heinous crime? Salute
Gurudev Shieldos says that he
He got a very strong shock and fell unconscious.
He went and by the time he regained consciousness Chayta was nearby
Everyone had been killed. Till now we have got Amrit
So I didn’t find it. then why did they do this
Did? Tai is there any problem? No. No.
No. I was just thinking that there was so much lava
Where did it come from? the same thing here for hundreds of miles
Not a volcano. Then where does the lava come from?
Went? Everybody it
See. What kind of grain is this? These
So is Lung's claw.
Impossible Loam then Daman in the East Sea
He is busy guarding the ring. There
No one can get out of it.
Gurudev, as far as I can remember, Western
The Queen of the Sea, Orangan, has a very
There is a special art which is called sky. tearing
claws means to cross the hour pass
Claws were used. there's lava here
This is the reason. I think it's from hell
He must have been brought here from hell. impossible,
His surveillance was then carried out by the people of the eastern sea
King is doing it. then there is only one possibility
It is saved. That must have happened to me which I got the most
Was very scared. The King of the Eastern Sea
I cheated. This is a very big allegation. We all
They could also be wrong. not at all.
This is their work.
Where are you going?
hey does that mean you are having fun? That
There is Kapal mountain on this side. Lums said that the citizens
committed a terrible crime by committing the massacre of
Is. No more talking to golden souls
It will be. First that will be over, then we can talk.
Kanha come with me to the palace and all the demons
Hunters should be called immediately. Why
Order? Tai's parents were killed by demons.
has given it. Now, before he does anything
Cause harm. Taking Veero along with him
Go back.
I know what you are going through.
But calm down for a little while
Table. Can I take you to the People's Palace first?
I talked to my father and Guru and decided to take this step
To the bottom of the matter. from that my mom and dad came back
Tell me will you come?
[music]
Please tell me this my mirror beauty is within 10 miles
Who is the fairest? It is you, Queen.
And who's the fairest in 100 miles? you only
Yes, Queen. In 1000 miles? You are there.
You are one in 10,000. you are the only one in the whole world
Are. Do you understand this? so much a lie
Don't say anything. No no I am not angry at you
wanted to do it. Listen to one thing. I am true
I don't get angry after hearing this. Really? Yes
I believe that I am the most beautiful woman.
But I know that you are more beautiful than me
There are women. ok then ask. Can I
Am I the fairest among women? No. Something
No. Tell me, in 10,000 miles, I
Am I the fairest? No. ok so 1000?
No way. owner? Not at all. 10m true
It is bitter. The fairest girl on Kamal mountain
It is me, right? Oh no. Do not do it. This
There is no other woman on the mountain. I
also she is a woman
Am. Only a woman is jealous of another woman.
You don't do it to me.
Demons come forward. Who called me a demon? I
Yes, Rani Shri ji.
[music]
you are children. Are we already there? Here
what have you come to do? Yes.
You will run away. Let me talk. I do
I will take it.
Are.
[music]
What happened?
[Appreciation]
[music]
Perhaps you do not know that this entire mountain
It's my body. If you have a daughter, how can I
Do you waste it?
[music]
If you exert yourself more than this, your body
Will be ruined. I said don't go down
[Appreciation]
The fire of anger has flared up. o yours this
So it was bad.
Thankfully it wasn't broken.
Thankfully, some part of me was saved. Today
If I survive, I will be able to fight tomorrow. rogue kid i
I will not leave you.
This is the next branch of the room.
[music]
I can't run away.
hey what happened kid?
Your body has become useless. to myself
Do you want to kill me? By the way this fire here
Who did you get hurt by? Neja makes ice, right? These
Who told you this? Barwa also taught everything
Is. Its powers are a combination of both.
Is this possible? Common man to spiritual pearl
I can't understand. and the two of us
Who is the Guru? you think i'm a liar
Am. Where do I have so much courage? but first
I sense the presence of demon power inside it
I had realised it. It is possible it might not be possible
Leave it. What are you saying uncle? I
Nothing. what did you have? what did you do
Was? Tell me what did you have? Hey, it was my uncle.
Don't do this. I can't stand the soil.
I saw it, I said
I have passed your test, today I am myself
I will do a special magic for your progress.
[music]
This has happened to me before. then i
I was very nervous. Perhaps the magic of progress
It went on for a very long time.
From this moment on, you are the Immortal Soul of the Moon Sect
Is.
[music]
[Appreciation]
This is the Yushu treasure vault which contains many
These are rare things. Sanjeevani herb
There are many things but you can choose only one
yes. I said Sanjivani Booti
[music]
The message of whatever the lungs have done 12
The spirits were sent in. Although the distance
Due to there being more, my brothers and sisters are here
Could not reach early. This time I'm on my own
I will go hunting for lungs. Now their
Well, no. did you tell them with me
Will you hunt? First I have to go to Chintang pass
Give it. Then I will take my money from Lang Raja
Revenge. Ok. I agree with what you say
Am. Now with your help we can destroy Lang Mahal
I will ruin it.
[music]
now to me
But I don't owe anyone any debt.
wait Neja i will get my body then i
I will take you to Lok Mahal myself. you know
yes what should I do?
It's hard out there because of you
Will increase. next time when
If we meet then we will not be enemies.
what karma
Is? You can't go. Otherwise your
The soul will be disintegrated.
Haley go.
[music]
Look, you calm down a little. you are well
Do you know. Nothing will change if you leave now
The one. Leave me alone. take me out here
From. I will not take it out. I promised the leader
I have promised to save you at any cost.
I was suffocating.
[Appreciation]
[music]
Who did all this? I am from the Chang Sect
Immortal soul forgets Yang Ogwang confesses crime
Is.
So you know Obiang is still alive
Is. You may punish me in whatever way you want but
Leave your son alone. Shut Up.
The Heavenly Court has punished your sect
entrusted with the task of imprisoning sea monsters
Was. Instead you destroyed Chatang Pass
Gave. Amnesty for the crime committed near Chatang
I will not get it. They must get justice today
will get.
[music]
Awaken the full power of the earth and sky
Let the world know what Bullion is
the thing is put them all in the tank
[music]
Bring it.
What did you do with the change pass? elder
Brother told me about Master Shen's orders, right?
Obey.
[Appreciation]
This reminds me of your current situation
But attention has to be paid.
Maharaj, we cannot stay here. If I
If you go to war then you will have to suppress the currency
Leave it to us. We are our powers
try our best to stop them
do. Ok.
[music]
Today
You are very powerful, but also stupid.
[music]
There is no better chance than this to take revenge
will get. Get out of hell and into the room
So ruin it.
[music]
Om
Sword
[music]
look at the idiots
Does this kind of running power scare you?
Is that you'll get caught? I say you
If you damage the Chintang pass
If you deliver me the tatters of your palace, I will
I will blow it away.
Tell me is my son alive?
[music]
remove it baba
[Appreciation]
[music]
get up
Om
[music]
I don't love life, I look at your body
For how long can he endure this? of my life
Don't worry. you your life
[Appreciation]
Save me. The time has come.
[music]
Look what you have done. Does your
Do you want to see everyone in the cab? Tell.
these chains
[music]
The King of Longs can match your power
Can't do it. So I am right about you
Was. You do what the community needs
have been. Your parents have been evil all their lives
Fought. From today, all their responsibilities are yours
We will handle this and eradicate the demons from their roots
I will give.
I promise I'll put them in bullets
By changing, I will take revenge for all of us. Now we
The palace will move. yes gurudev.
[music]
All
Neja Neja Neja Neja Neja Neja Papa Neja
Mother Neza
[music]
Neja my child are you okay
your body
[music]
She already knew about you and Robin.
He knows everything.
me me
I thought I would never meet you.
[music]
Till then Gurudev is doing magic
Keep it entangled.
Leja dad has nothing to do with it.
Because he is the real culprit. Our
Soul Forgetting
[music]
Make portions.
People, I have met you after a long time Bullia
you are here
How the hell did you meet me with my lungs
Oh, I must ask about the betrayal
What is your intention behind imprisoning my father?
Is? Who said I have imprisoned him?
Only you know about my family
Are. If you didn't order then Nessa
and the demon hunters killed my father
Why were you imprisoned? and my little brother felt it
Arrows and those arrows were made by your own disciples
made
Was. It is because of your art that I
You were recruited. from your eyes
Nothing!
I would have survived. Because for you for so many years everything has been
Why did you do good and bad deeds? I guessed it
I can imagine that you have seen this chaos near you
why did you create a ruckus? You put this debris on the head of the lungs
You want to put it, right? You are your brother and teacher
That you are repaying my kindness like this. Me
Used it for his own benefit. Our
There is only a relationship of enmity between them.
I can make a deal with you, immortal soul Bholi.
Being the caretaker of U Shiv Mahal
You must know the magic to open these chains
It must be so. It comes. But what do you want?
You will betray me. thousands of years ago
All four of us were involved in the war with heaven.
So who will keep you imprisoned in hell after deceiving us?
Delivered? Now Wuliang and Gong are the target
He is making it and we also want the same. heard
Was that the immortal soul Valiyang was not biased
And who can know this better than you?
Is? If you can free us from the hell of Hades
If you help us to become immortal by getting it, then we will
Will always support you. as well as spiritual
Will also tell about Modi and donation shells. spiritual
Modi and both the goals are too much. your last
What happened to the vow to fight till death? then we
young and immature
Were. Thousands of years of imprisonment have taught us this
given that the king and his
what the laws were
Are. You are wise. But when you take care of your own people
If you can betray me then how can I trust you? Bus
The only way I can get over you is by being ready
Are.
[music]
So all three people went to Williang on their own will
got ready to take the curse of. if he
If you do not obey his orders then he will never
It could also take their life. Then he gave them
To free me from the chains of hell's pain
I fulfilled my promise. Whenever any power
If it rises it will commit similar massacre
convict someone else and punish him
He gets it for me. Shagong Bau has said that he
He has already done such work for him so that
Williang joins him in the Jana sect
Can give a chance to happen. This time Wuliang
by destroying the Chatang Pass and shifting its fault to the east
on the sea longs and for all this
During that time those three people were busy making kings slaves
It was successful. What's more, Vyang has spiritual
You can also know the difference between salvation and demon from him.
Took it. After that he deliberately killed two idiots
left it like that which went to Yushumen
Can you tell me what exactly happened?
[music]
When there was no hope left then Shagulga
Made a plan. He sent Yaksha
saved us and hid us in the sewer
Gave. Right time to take it out again
Waited for . what about you? My own someone
No. Now there is no meaning in living.
[music]
the demons that hunters capture and bring
not put into the correctional facility at Yushu Palace
as it seems to the common people, rather they
are put into the Dayang pool where they are
Wuliang turns them into pills of immortality
so that the power of the Jan sect is strengthened
what have you done, such a bad thing
How can you follow Gurudev's teachings?
What happened? How will you face them? now when
You must have found out about Wulian's deeds.
if he is gone then before it is too late
Take them to Youshu Palace so that the Almighty can punish them
Give.
The demon hunters were killed by Buliang himself
Have given training. What does he think of us
Will you support us if you say so?
So I was wrong about the rooms.
Was. leave it
[music]
These. I will help.
You have betrayed us. learnt it from you
Yes, elder brother. boys to save the people
There was no other way at that time. you this
Do you know. to protect myself at this time
I don't have any way out either.
Don't leave me. What will happen to us now?
So you're all sold out.
[music]
south sea long
King Long of the North Sea
[music]
Raja Long Queen of the Western Sea
Come play with Jacha.
[music]
So here it is.
This is my affair
[music]
how will you take it? 100 times? 200 times or 300
fold?
[music]
Did you enjoy it? Nonsense. Nothing happens to me.
Your body is raw. don't stress so much
Apply. This is my mistake. and to the lungs
Nessa can even give her life to free him
Is. young and immature
yes. Let me play a little with you
small.
[Appreciation]
[music]
Don't you feel ashamed in teasing the child? Oye
How did you feel your brother's hand?
[music]
This won't work. It seems difficult. Then
Let's put something different. how will the smoke be
Tell? Excellent.
Take hold of it
Them. Escaping from attackers.
So you are hiding here.
Hey be careful I am here. my brother forgive me
Do it. intelligence
Surprise
Transforming magic
I'm crazy I'm not stupid
How did you two come to be? Who ripened? Who ripened on the tree?
Who doesn't know about papaya on feet?
so you
no sure
[music]
it would be fun
came and
tell me papaya is ripe after catching it
brewing
ripe papaya ripe sheep or ripe
Papaya I am the real one and I don't want anything else
Address. Just made it.
You should have made it a little easier. How much
It's difficult.
Fool, I am not my brother, you are the money.
Hey I am Hasiya Shanu. sit quietly. to you
Who doesn’t know? You don't know either. Oho
So I am Mahbiya.
There is a limit. Life energy flows in loss.
The fire of Samadhi melts the gold.
This is how the whole bullet is made sharp and
Powerful.
[music]
[Appreciation]
Why are you afraid? hey we are in lava
Used to take dips. Something
Hey, this is the real fire of Samadhi.
What are you looking at like that? if anyone could eat it
If it is, it's just me.
Leave my father alone.
Settle down.
[music]
Is the Spirit Pearl the same size as the Demon Pill
the same powerful
Hey
[music]
Go yes, a heart winning hobby. Because I
I know your real identity. what do you think
You have a way to escape me
No? This cannot happen. This Shah is very
He is a seller. When did you do this?
O this is why the magic of progress takes so long
Was. This is your doing.
[music]
Come
Listen to something special, now both the spheres and the heart
The tearing curse cannot be broken so quickly
will find 1000 thorns in your veins and blood
It is in the nerves. Now you can move as much as you want
Same number of prawns. I understood it
In? Now I know of your presence
Why didn't I realize it? because you
Had turned into stone. If you stay alive then Neja
will only suffer loss.
spiritual
Modi and Demon Kola very precious treasures
Are. I want to treat them well
Was. But now these will be made into bullets.
Oh father you are still alive
This is Bullion's heart winning curse and
This is why Lungs was accused of the Shatan pass
The leader has been cheated, he has been given no opinion
Do whatever you want to do with me, my mother
Baba is not at fault
Killing you won't change anything.
[music]
We are all going to die here. If still
If anyone is upset, he can tell me.
[music]
Brother Uliang Moon Sect has a lot of reputation
Is it good. How can you do such a disgusting thing
You can and don't make any mistake. why don't you
Go and confess it before the Almighty. I
I will apologize for you.
I have never seen a fool like you. If immortal
Are souls safe in this world or are you
Do even half the hard work of useless demons
If I had taken it, I would have wasted so much time and effort
had he done it he would have been saved. Now whether it means that I
Why should I not become infamous and ruined? all this
I have seen the Moon Sect as powerful
have done to make it. My
certainty certainty certainty
My determination is absolutely firm.
Another one got burnt. I will not be able to eat this.
Here, eat you. Thank you. when my wings
You can eat them when they are ripe. Punjabi
It is absolutely ready. to divide us amongst ourselves
Needed Hey what is happening? My
What is happening to the body?
Oho
So
mine save me.
Stay calm. Save your energy by staying calm.
Keep enduring as long as you can.
[music]
My child, your power is greater than mine
Is. You can do this. if you rip out the heart
If you can endure till the curse ends
Maybe I can get out of here. heart breaker
The curse lasts for six hours. daddy me
I don't think I would be able to endure this much.
Queen Mother are you okay?
Nezha
Mother I am fine. you guys never give up
Accept. Don't worry about us. you complete
lump your Head. I am alright! Mother save me from fire
nothing is happening. Nobody cares for my child
could kill. monster shells if i'm not wrong
And the source of the real fire of Samadhi is only one
Is. This means Bayan Kund will harm you
I can't deliver it. right its all my fault
Is.
I got cheated. This is just my avatar
Is. Just as I suspected. destroy both shells
Cannot be done. Maybe that's why the Almighty
had to come himself
[Laughter]
Was.
Neja you are doing great son.
Why don't you get a chance to prove yourself?
If you get a chance. Swallow the dissolving tablet.
Then I will leave your parents.
Ok. Of course I am cruel, but my
I fulfill my promises. Otherwise, all these demons
Do not swear loyalty to me. Bus
You swallow this pill. Then I'm yours
leave the parents
[music]
Give. What is this you are doing? you to the child
You are threatening to kill his parents.
If you call yourself an immortal soul then give me peace
yes.
[music]
Nija even if we die but you
Have to stay alive. stand firm until the curse is broken
Stay or wait for your brothers.
Do you think that I will crush both the balls?
I can't kill. It's just a matter of time.
It is too late for you to die. I will see again
Who will save you?
[music]
I don't want to die in vain. You
why don't you let me die
are? I want to die for you. If
You even embraced death to save us
so do you think that we will ever
Will you be able to live in peace?
No mother.
You may get hurt. No problem. time is near
Is. I want to hug you one last time
Am. Maybe I won't see you grow up
I will be able to So today is
You have to follow the path you create.
[music]
Come on
Om Om
[music]
[Appreciation]
I am useless, worthless
Am. I was born a demon
I just troubled you.
I wanted karma on me
[music]
yes. This is all my fault. Forgive me
Mother. Please forgive me.
[music]
I am always happy with you no matter what
I will stay.
I don't care
Was. are you a grandfather or immortal
Soul. Just know now that
You are my beloved son and I am yours
I will always be with you.
[music]
What
Majora, calm down son. just do it otherwise
Your body will explode.
[music]
[Appreciation]
Look at the back
[music]
The real fire of Samadhi has created the body
The fire required for this has been compensated. Nezha
the body of
Now it is completely ready.
[music]
daddy take care of mom
Keep. Will you help in breaking the goons?
[music]
Oh no, those people are using the energy of Tahiyan Kund
I am sleeping. The great pool is
[music]
Many hunters will attack on my orders
Dad, you should save your energy. Very
We have been serving as servants since time immemorial. I thought
If we give our all, they will help us to live
will give. But look, he wants to kill us.
If that is what they want, then it is okay.
till our last breath
Will fight. We will fight.
[Appreciation]
Can't let them come out.
[music]
[Appreciation]
Don't give up, try your best. Om
[music]
Let us go
[Appreciation]
[music]
My
The foundation of the Mann Sect was shaken.
[music]
send all these traitors to hell
Two. Ours
[Appreciation]
[music]
wow
Hey sir this is too much this is wrong I don't know how to talk
You guys like our
[music]
protruding
Lu means his two pawns are also demons.
Demons, immortal souls, all this is a result of his conspiracy
It is just a part. what do you think of yourself
To? by obeying my command
Look at the denial.
[music]
[Appreciation]
Now let me show you my real power.
[music]
Om
[Appreciation]
[music]
I'm giving you one last chance because I
I respect the warriors. surrender
If you do it, you will achieve immortality. and got it
Immortality. What if I am both?
Happened? You call yourself everyone's husband. But
You take advantage of the weak and
You create a ruckus. In reality, Tamā is the root of evil.
of immortal souls on this foolish and idiot world
It's a secret. Only strong people can save you
will find it. Agree or else this is the place to run away
It will fall short. If there is shortage of space then I will
make room
I will take it. If you don't accept me, I
I will overthrow the government.
[music]
Gurudev my face my face idiots
broke the spell of my whole life.
I will break your face old man.
[music]
Let's go back to the palace
Let us go. I'm coming too.
[music]
[Appreciation]
My father was in the deep sea with Lung
They are going to hide. Now that you come into sight
If you are done then why aren't you with us
Go?
No. I was silent all my life and then
The way to escape was over. But now
I will not run away, I will face the world.
That organ is one of the most powerful immortal souls
and is trusted by the Almighty. They
He will not give up easily. Demons and Immortals
The paths of souls are different. as if water
And fire. Immortal souls demons. these words are
These are excuses to control the weak.
Just what will you do? What do you think?
You can change it.
I will try.
Now it seems that we have to fight this world
that I will not age. Obing
[music]
[Appreciation]
I know once you make a decision
If you take it, you stick to it.
My child, earlier I put a lot of pressure on you
I kept it and did not try to understand that
What do you think? forgive me
Give. To be honest, you have a good life
My purpose was to give. But I've
saw that the experience of the older generation has passed
It's about tomorrow which may not work for you
Do. You make your own path
will be. So from today onwards, always speak your heart
Hear
[music]
Om
I knew you would come back
how because in our age
Fear is not allowed.
[music]
Show So
Joy Roma
No control show off
[music]
Research Function
Take it empty, mother
[music]
Naan
Go
[music]
So
khushhan
What
[music]