HINA FILM ADMINISTRATION
A M ADMINISTRATION
V]
KA
. Blessed by heaven and earth,
the Chaos Pearl was born.
The Supreme Lord split it into two.
The celestial energy within became the Spirit Pearl,
while the demonic energy formed the Demon Orb.
A Wrath of Heaven curse was cast on the Demon Orb,
set to destroy it with lightning in three years.
Later, due to Shen Gongbao's intervening,
the Demon Orb reincamated as Nezha, third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass.
the Demon Orb reincarnated as Nezha, third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass.
the Demon Orb reincarnated as Nezha, third son of Li
the Demon Orb reincarnated as Nézha, third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass.
The Spirit Pearl became Ao Bing, also the third son Of the dragon king.
The Spirit Pearl became Ao Bing, also the third son of the Dragon King.
the two became best friends.
Nezha, influenced by his parents,
ss demonic nature,
and saved Chentang Pass.
Together with Ac Bing.
Together with Ao Bing,
they faced the Wrath of Heaven,
they faced the Wrath of Heaven, ) | a EY
and at last
“bang uid at de fF
RIVE
IIE
1 Wlles wWeredestroyed. ..
Res were destiy
[AF
I . the soul will soon fade into oblivion.
the soul will sgpn fade into oblivAoT
Zag
your physic ¥orms.
your physicHl Yofms.
your physical fg
A J
-
I a. A EET BE ie hb
LagatStartup! T Wl
TP" Smethifigsofi..
Is there”
to make your bodies.
Did you just scratch your feet
Oh, don't worry. A
Oh, don't worry. \b
I don't mind sticky foot, a quick wash will fix it. N \
I don't mind sticky foot, a quick wash will fix it. , ' \
It's not your foot | care. —_
= ivsnotyour®Pcare. TT
[3
It's not your foot | care.
—
Did you just blow your nose with that hand?
} No, nothing.
No, nothing.
It's just lotus powder.
LotuSperider.
It's ready to go.
Here, come on.
One booger for each of you.
| mean one serving.
FF. rr "gp  Fchd®hop! To save your souls.
BN Tey VV 3
POE WW PMAn the ass, little bastard!
What is this?
Thanks to you. y
i've been look
I've been looki
. Time for shaping. .
“Te
-da,
Vita Rd 1M. 2
w) BVAtom Ji “Faget
Thanks, Piggy.
SS ~eaeaove notfikedyet. aad BS
I've mobilized all of Chentang's forces ;
I've mobilized all of Chentang's forces
puarding of Shen Gongbao and the Eastern Sea dragons.
on guarding of Shen Gongbao and the Eastern Sea dragons.
The dragons are watching the
b dragons are watching the Abyss monsters,
none of which would escape.
Shen Gongbao alone is no threat.
You should check this out.
isn't this impeccable?
Isn't this impeccable?
Woah! N
Woah!
He learned from the best.
does it have to b®Bxactly the same?
Can't you make me look better?
Huh?
-+ mgParents always pray good for kids, huh?
Parents always pray good for kids, huh? -—
Make me tall and hunky.
Tvs,
pay Ye. TEES Joule
i fwike Up your mind?
Tall and hunky, LE
With a touch of handsameness.
With a touch of handS8Eness.
Meng and lofty.
Yet super adorable.
your performance then.
| should've tkeR
DIY is always the best
DIY is always the be ]
td take a whil®}
Let's do you first.
[2
'
Let's dn vou first. y
$0 you must be tempered by pure water, he 2000
Wired by pure water.
fine-tuning will talfEe
prone for now?
e first versio
pahnthe first version,f
jagree. (WINS. oo 9. x
You were born of the fire element,
Iho tire flames.
el in pure flames.
A WB Tew 4S 77
Enemy has been spotted at sea.
It seems to be ShegGongbao.
y 4 It seems to be Shen Gongbao.
EE 3
\ UE
IE aa Carry on with your spell.
Carry on with your spell.
We'll handle the intr
Master immort
POE” $7 Before anoffBNIIEPRe stick is fully burnt,
pudgy unten iiss
your body won TEP IKPOR
to what do we owe this honor?
I
Ehow of my plan with|
FI! low 0 my plan wit baporll
FERN ow of my plan wit bao
FOREnow of my plan wit bagorl
BIT: helgibut feel un...ud y
Bt hel} but feet un...uRY. |
Chomang uss it neiwily ©
Chentang Pass is heavily guarded,
and Master Taiyi is within the city.
, won't accomplish muc
, alone, won't accomplish much.
od i'm alone?
y. wad d I'm alone? wo
I'm alone?
fm alone?
If they find out about the Spirit Pearl,
not only will you fail to avenge your son,
not only will you fail to avenge your son, -
but the entire Eastern Dragon Clan
but thowill begotherbl@wme, ran
will bear the blame.
you'll be cast into the abyss purgatory,
surrounded by all your old "fellows".
I Let's see how we welcome you.
Let's see how we welcome you.
Being stuck in Dragon Palace...
How:could you avenge your son?
How could you avenge your son?
Even | feel nervous for you.
You fools are in nop iNN
You fools are in ho place to gloat.
* You fools are in no place to gloat.
You fools are in no place to gloat.
| was simply trying to help.
P | was simply trying to help.
But it seems that you
don't appreciate it.
You must've forgotten what Umi capable of.
_ You must've forgotten what i'm capable of.
iad
You must've forgotten what I'm capable of. ‘
1 know this ase.
The Sky... Sky.a Sky...
Sky Splitting Claw.
Thank you.
Master Shen can take this claw to Chentang Pass,
Master Shen can take this claw to Chentang Pag »
and use it to tear opens rift leading back to me.
and use it to tear open a rift leading back to me.
and use it to tear open a rift leading back to me. A
The Abyss Monsters can then help you destroy your enemy.
~~ TheAbyss Monsters can then hillbu destroy your enemy.
The Abyss Monstes® can then helpJou destroy your enemy.
The Abyss Monsters can then help you destroy your enemy.
&78 Can then help you destroy your enemy.
NF TheAbys
The Abyss Monsters?
How... is that possible?
were trapped by the Suppression Seal for thousand years. \
They were trapped by the Suppression Seal for thousand years.
How could they possibly escape? a
The dragons... have they already released them?
A” BB The dragons... have they already released them? WS
ep-Stabilizing Chains binding us,
FEED ne chance lor escape.
y | theve's no chance for escape. (a Johan gu. ©
there's no chance for escape.
Thisisawinwinacuc NIA ad === 2 @
#7 Thig&awinwin tactic.
p win-win tactic.
What do you say, my brother?
You wouldn't be so generous.
Tous.
Get to the point.
What's your price?
In this purgatory,
where flames burn our bodies,
every day feels like a year.
If you could slightly lower the lava's heat,
if you could slightly lower the lava's heat,
easing our suffering,
we'd be willing to serve you with all our might.
we'd be willing to serV®you with all our might.
we'd be willing to se
we'd be willing to serve
_ What's going on?
What is Shen Gonghao up to now?
Finally, we're out! Yay!
SS Byebye
Bye-bye!
How will we explain this to General Li now?
Luckily no one saw us.
What for?
I'll break you arms
and then you break my legs.
We'll say the Yaksha did it.
When the general sees how badly we're hurt,
he won't blame us anymore.
Try your best.
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Master Immortal,
you're here!
He let the Yaksha get away!
It was all your fault.
Who are you to point fingers?
Who are you to play innocent?
Oh my,
mb and Dumber!
Dumb and Dumber!
You two boneheads!
Get over here and guard me!
Yes, Sir! Right away!
-h = _, «
-—
Show no mercy. '
Shéw no mercy.
Shen Gongbao!
Ao Bing is not dead.
Chentang Pass and the dragons have no reason to fight.
Taiyi is rebuilding Ao Bing's body right now.
EE 7 <A. TY GR
Liar! »n
The shield...
Ao Bing!
- Master Taiyi has built me a new body.
Please, ceasetire
Shen
I saved your disciple.
How will you thank me?
“P's Nezha in there? ®
that's Nezha in there?
Why, you ungrateful bastard!
They must die!
You think you can break this shield?
X ou think you can break this shield?
Ao Bing! A
ols sl. A YE
. . hi
(failed the mission to save o
Noneuof¢hat matters. >
rid Ant you to be safe.
1jo®Want you to be safe.®
AS{ONp as you're here,
it's enough for me. L.
it's enough for me. N
Your body, gH is...
Please, he's literally a newborn.
How could he take a hit like that?
Ho could he yhnt Dee that”
Hey! it's not ready yet!
Ao Bing, what's P Bing on?
Never move before fixed.
If your body exceeds its limit,
it will collapse!
For heaven's sake...
Make another bod
Making two bodies back-to-back hy ~~
has completely drained the Sacred Lotus's energy. 5
has completely drained the Sacred Lotus's energy.
Without a body, won't his soul scatter?
Master, do something!
there's nothing | can do.
PEN YN AB oMouryiace as the Spirit Pearl, | deserve tAIS: .
CC EN NF toModrpiace as the Spirit Pearl. | deserve this.
BN CO \ WER. Ifmysacrifice
an bring you back to life,
-\Y an bring you back to life,
BY JMR then it's a fair price to pay.
-_— hy yy J en it's a fair price to pay.
Who asked you to?
| am happy being the Demon Orb.
I am happy being the Demon Orb.
Ay a please spare Chentang Pass. NW.
a s please spare Chentang Pass. ) yy
We should stop the mistakes. )
We should stop the mistakes.
This is my final wish. *
This is my final wish. ‘
This is my final wish.
There has to be other ways.
¥ You! Try harder! Fb.
You! Try harder! hh
Ao Bing share your body for now.
Share your body.
TT Ay
} Two souls sharing one body,
—-—, . | . Two souls sharing one body,
ru rejection is inevitable.
Tay WW §  rejectionisinevitable.
earl and Demon Orb come from the same source.
The Spirit Pearl and Demon Orb come from the same source.
Sharing one body
-n days shouldn't t
for seven days shouldn't be a problem.
That's (t!
: ia
rT Fre 5
This feels... strange...
Ao Bing, are you here?
Yes, [am
I can hear your voice in my head!
| can hear your voice in my head!
Bh But this is only a temporary fix. yr
But this is only a temporary fix. ;
What happens alter seven days?
What happens after seven days? F ’
There's some potion in the vault of Yu Xu Palace.
Elixir Reparo.
Itcanres the divine power of magical items.
It can restore the divin
With it,
the Sacred Lotus will bloom
red Lotus will bloom
the Sacred Lotus will hi
But how will you obtain it?
I'll go to the Supreme Lord himself and beg for it.
Or are you planning to
report on me and the dragons?
The Supreme Lord wouldn't sa... save a son of the dragons.
If asking 8oesn't work.
. If asking doesn't work,
A then we'll just take. Fy + -.
Yu Xu Palace is at the core of the Chan Sect, ,
Yu Xu Palace is at the core of [EIEN
= protected by formidaiBgmwers. & = le 2
protected by formidieppwers. / = ll
I : ‘ll break into the Court of Heaven if | had to.
EY 7 I'll break into the Court of Heaven if Ihad to.  ’
Your Majesty. calimdownd = @&a ® 2 MR
HEGEL, Or Uh.
I might have a plan. A | |
Imighthaveaplan. &F a BRA \ ER
Chan disciples who excel in their traig he.
Chan disciples who excel in their trai
can participate in the Ascension Trial. ; 4 i rr a
can participate in the Ascension Trial. - F
the Ascension Trial.
Passing the trial grants not only immortality,
Passing the triabgrants not only immortality,
but also the right to choose one
but also the right to choose one fw
ma... magic item from the Yu Xu Vault as a res
ma... magic item from the Yu Xu Vault as a reward.
Are you suggesting
Nezha participate in the trial
to obtain the elixir?
No, no, no!
He's beaming with demonic energy!
As soon as he uses his powers, he'll be exposed!
Isn't Ao Bing sharing Nezha's body?
“4 len't Ao Bing sharing Nezha's body?
is In#¥ura can mask the demonic energy perfectly.
8 is*dlving'Bura can mask the demonic energy perfectly.
As long as he passes the tril within seven days,
As long as he passes the t L ithin seven days,
not only will we havethe el... elixi
not only will we havelilje el... elixir...
not only will we have JIE el... elixir...
achieveimmii SERDAR ~° =
Then I'm not a demon anymore?
This will save both Ao Bing and Nezha.
Eve... everyone is happy.
" This isn't the right thing to do.
Then what do you suggest?
Follow the rules. L)
Follow the rules.
Come clean with the Supreme Lord
and trust his judgement.
My wife and | will also plead for mercy, «®
My wife and | will also plead for mercy,
so the sins of the parents don't affect the children.
so the sins of the parents don't affect the children. | [| \ yf
so the sins of the parents don't affect the children. | VY ]
Mere mortals,
you have only decades of life experience, wg, oN
you have only decades of life experience,
how dare you lecture me about morality?
S—
how dare you lecture me about morality Lb a W | EES ~~
how dare you lecture me about morality? SE
how dare you lecture me about morality?
Longer than | could remember,
‘ I've lived for thousands of years.
I've lived for tholisands of years.
I've lived for thousands of years.
Let me tell you one truth and one truth only.
) I'll have Chentang Pass sink with him.
I'll have Chentang Pass sink with him.
Stop!
Ao Bing is my friend.
Sw WN ® AoBingismyfriend. R®re
EE A B® Twill save him for sure. TRE
ED SO yO dare to harm Chent PE
I [fF emesh your Dragon PATE
Except for Nezha and Taiyi,
no one leaves Chentang Pass fom no *‘ &®
no one leaves Chentang Pasgfdmflowon. =
no one leaves Chen
fI'in sever ay don't see Elixir Reparo }
7 & orthenew®of my clan gets out,
ff orthdnew®of my clan gets out,
or the new® of my clan gets out,
EY J Il lB hentang Pass
w= ET rnd chentang Pass
f &ink forever.
I don't trust my siblings,
andlcan't stay out of my body for long.
and I can't stay out of my body for long.
and | can't stay out df my body for long.
The fate of Chentang Pass
is inyour hands.
SX Sy
There's no message that can't bdfonveyed
There's no message that can't bdAW ed
with justanod.
we're all here to say goodbye to Young Master Nezha.
we're all here to say goodbye to Young Master NeZha.
we're all here to say goodbye to Young Master Néha.
We want to thank him for saving the entiregity.
We want to thank him for saving the entire city,
You're too kind.
My son has caused enoug
over the years.
| always knew the Young Master was destined for greatness.
1 always knew the Young Master was destined for greatness.
Look at him,
aLam crenmd,
a wide forehead,
prominent nose,
full cheeks and thick lips.
All signs of a true hero!
I've never been
{'ve never been wrong in reading faces.
Young Master, remember to brush your teeth after meals!
g Master, remember to brush your teeth after meals!
the Demon Slayers is now re-branded as the Nezha Gang.
players is now re-branded
members will follow yoll
’ All members will follow your orders.
All members will follow your orders.
Young Master, want to practice calligraphy?
Young Master, want to practice calligraphy? Fg
I'm here for you!
Young Master, you're three years old now. :
It's time to get a girlfriend.
Any interests in instrument? yf
We're proficient in all of them. Ff v0
We're proficient in all of them. al |
play shuttlecock.
Pll play with you.
J'll play with you.
Didn't you always want to play shuttlecock with me?
Didn't you always want to play shuttiecock with me?
Well... ~
ard on the kicks.
Ha ha ha!
=~ I'ma general of war!
That's my boy!
we do it another day?
Why stop when you're having fun?
a It's fine. I'm fine.
"It's fine. I'm fine.
I'll join too!
My lady, you don't have to do this
you looking down on me?
I'm also a general of war!
catch this!
how did you miss that?
If only | weren't the Demon Orb...
TR What was that?
It's time to go.
| Before you go,
EE will you give your mother
a big hug?
a] Please, people are watching.
Please, people are watching.
Here are some snacks | made.
i Here are some snacks | made.
For you and your master on the road.
Okay, okay.
I'm not on board yet!
Your body isn't fully fi<ed
Your body isn't fully fixed.
Don't use too much force.
Alright, alright.
And watch your temper.
Try to stay calm out there.
Without me and your father by your side,
learn to take care of yourself.
You silly child.
What's wrong with just a hug?
That's too much,
It's not a farewell any
Let's
mov
e
TLE OTSEY-  Tistebad? 0000 aad
y w-—y 4 Foogl, food, food. -
y ave you thought about how to pass the trial? oo J
Have you though} about how to pass the trial?
) What is the trial about?
yp What is the trial about? hr
progress of your cultivation.
SRT progress of your cultivation.
SW $4000 mrt defeat, terehanded,
three demon kings of earth-mpnster level.
three demon kings of earth-monster level.
Fighting...
That's my specialty} ¢ [
But as soon as you give off demonic en ,
your identity will be exposed.
Just let Ao Bing control my body.
Just let Ao Bing control my body. ©
His divine energy
I will be just as powerful. -
Ee etsy. mT ld
Pol end fight me.
} Ao Bing, what are you doing?
p=
. When a soul inhabits another body, A
Jus fut isn
Y WJ  Don'tpmid WN
coming...
I'm coming...
Having fun, HIRI
~ hy
ST —,.
Op acting like a reckless teenager.
BR Stop acting like a reckless teenager,
—
| The Sleepy-Slumber Pill. ’ Ba
PV The Sleepy-Slumber Pill.
What's that?
Take this, and you'll fa
Takethis,andyou'llfallasieepfiAAMEEEEN. {1 WWW!’
a. |] BY =i
> 4
PRESAIE can fully control youTgspmys
can fully control your bit
d
odili've told me...
mT A w=
LF 3
Master Taiyi?
, eT = e\ $11 wd
Now this feels like the real deal. -
Now this feels like the real deal. a
What's wrong?
LXY  ®Hhtwery 0N
EN
al Mietely taken over Nezha'shollJii ES 00
-—
} completly taken Sver Nezha's
This time, | won't hold back.
IY ™ W ’ This time, | won't hold back.
Ig WV Ww This time, | won't hold back.
You'd better give it your all, too.
Barely able to match my skills.
L 4. Tooheatyrecently. \ $2 WAY. Wd
L-  Reedmorewaterr. 2 € YL
| -.  T RN irdeal. VF WL
ulin fountain! We're here.
IW Kunlun Mountain! We're here.
hd " Iheard a day here :
gar in the mortal world.
the mortal world.
~
ot in the celestial realm yet.
Berrys famous across the world,
The jasper.
, aLhan Sect immortal.
credential@fpgehan Sect immortal. .
you'll receive respect e here you
J
SEEN on an immortal is amazing.
AN TY. ! our brothers have ascended,  °
Both of your brothers have ascended.
You'll have no problem either.
I mean Nezha's brothers.
His two brothers p
; ERA TE
JPR
joie 3
ve dams
N Lo jes about his brothers
to set a good example for him.
Let me tell you something,
-— atin Nezha idolizes his brothers.
A} Nezha idolizes his brothers.
+ tomeetthe ong
n the tand, hunting down a A. SE
demons that wreak havoc on humanity, EE
keeping the world at
SS YR
iho Demon Hunters ro
REE |cader of the DEMOIE
Briple of Immortal
Isn't his predecessor Shen Gongbao?
what's that smoke over there? rl y Ww
what's that smoke ovefe B
FF
That's the most precious trealire oi
FATS fr)
p been in charge of Yu Xu Palaces
Fo /  I'vebrought my disciple to participate in the Asce
UTOTENL \
RPTIER
| 7 WE” Master Wuliang
12 TEER
Bull of robust vita
What do you think you' red IEPE
:
ha
vo@f
=1
vol f
Jedieatt
Pp BW Restroom 0 2 T W@W
A! GEAY  iswhereyoupee.
is where you pee. oH )
PSN | 2c ade of jade? ov
ITM A a lace made of EIR
vy, 44
TOREhow where the ré SU
al
SE
evement for the Sect.
CC AndUEEIB.: achievement for
HI
RIVES
us Anan bad
Telly, it fakes six dB RIARIEE
or 1 Ie
YET INT BR
PYLE PISI4) ULE
A My disciple is a bit crude.
F.-~~ B Wydisdpleis a bit crude. |
Please forgive him. pr i
ai A A BA DIENCTIXIE
OVE UCU WEEE: isa bit c79F tal “|
W.se forgive him. 0 add
Brother,
I PY |
["
pis of the essence.
Let's have a few mOTeRIgM
SEN RIINPP EP
pe
Why stop?
It's been six hours,
Master Shen.
Too tired to continue.
Cultivation allows no laziness.
Without my permission
you'll never s
General Li Jing of Chentang Pass is here to see you.
Master Shen,
yesterday's battle
left many soldiers and civilians of Chentang Pass injured.
We've run out of medicine.
| humbly ask you to open a pat )
| humbly ask you to open a path
so that a few doctors can
so that a few doctors can leave the city to
so that a few doctors can leave the city t8 i
No wdTider you're...
Who did that?
St... stop, stop, stop!
He escaped the city during the battle.
General Lj, please,
General Li, please,
’ take him ba... back with you.
take him ba... back with you.
This is a misunderstanding, Master Shen!
a demon too!
1 captured HWaksha™
Now that i
and since he hasn’
and since he hasn't done anything worse,
I'm just a small role.
| don't think you understood me.
~~ Idon" think you understood me.
~~ Noone léhves here, not even a demon.
~~ Noone lehyes here, not even a demon.
No one Raves here, not even a demon.
% Let alone humans.
Master Shen, please have mercy.
We are both villains!
I'm n... not a villain. —-
not a villain.
Everyone who knows the secret of the Spirit Pearl
Everyone who knows the secret.of the Spirit Pear!
must stay here.
Without medicine,
the injured won't survive.
Master Shen, please,
I'm only asking to save lives. '
Sir!
This man came from outside the city,
and he injured some of our soldiers.
Lock... lock him up too.
Brother.
Brother, is that you?
Brother, it's me!
You haven't been home for centuries. -
You haven't b od) home for centuries. .
What are you doing here?
Father sent me to find you.
the compass you gave me.
It tells me where you are.
how is he doing?
or how is he doing?
Ever since you entered Yu Xu Palace,
father's been full of energy,
father's been i Il of energy,
like he took some mir®®tonic. =~
You are the only one from our village ever
made it as a Chan Sect immortal.
Now, fellow demons from miles around
are pouring in to train with father.
ng in to train with father.
By the way,
y are you here?
Didn't you promise me before,
once I've achieved human form,
ou'd get me into Yu Xu Palace? =
ou'd get me into Yu Xu Palace®.
Look! | can turn into a human now!
All these years, I've trained so hard,
never rested a day.
Glory to Yu Xu, answering heaven's call.
Travel the world, bringing justice to all.
Say, brother,
what are you doing here?
Are these sea monsters your subordinates?
Are these sea sters your subordinates?
EE Why are you surrounding Chentang Pass?
Well, about that...
Laste S ding Chentar
en is defending Ch
Master Shen is defending Chentang Pass.
Evil forces invaded the city.
Master Shen and the sea clan came to our aid.
On behalf of my people, | thank you for this noble act.
Don't m@ntion it.
Brother, you're incredible!
Is this the demon attacking Chentang Pass?
Ah!
| u are a disgrace to all demons!
You are a disgrace to all demons!
Hey,
can you
wait a few more year
wait a few more years
before going to Yu Xu Palace?
I ~~n transform ins a human now!
| can transform into a human now!
It's just that. |
I'm preparing for my promotion to the Twelve Golden Immortals,
so | can't be distracted.
oT Twelve Golden Immortals?
} Twelve Golden Immortals?
Once
Once it's done,
I'll take vou t
okay?
r promotion is more i
CLIT ES TC Yo Xu Pala
| can go to Yu Xu Palace anytime.
| haven't quite mastered the shape-shifting.
I'll go back and practice more.
Moro, -
this is what I've saved up since | entered the palace.
Sal disciples these immortality pills.
ps all disciples these immortality pills.
Yu Xu Palace gives all disciples these immortality pills.
. gain ten years' worth of cultivation.
gain ten years' worth of cultivation.
this is too precious.
Brother, you're training for a promotion.
_..you should bring them hack.
You... you should bring them back.
Share them with the family.
Father will blame me.
are you not obeying your big brother? =
Take the pills and leave now.
This is the front line.
If... if you stay,
I'll be distracted.
I'll leave.
You must make it into the Twelve Golden Immortals.
You must make it into the Twelve Golden immortals.
Vou mo timake i nto the Twelve Golden imimaort
I'll keep training myself.
you... you bring him back, too.
1 wasn't helping you. ; “
1 was helping the young one.
| was helping the young one.
A good role model
can change his life.
can change his life. “=
Le.,. leave me a list of medicines you need
Le... leave me a list of medicines you need,
I oY UY i
| am Nezha, the Third Prince bold.
{ am Nezha, the Third Prince bold.
I FAT
I still eating?
~~ wwey vous doomed.
~~ SESE» $$ Yous doomed. 0
EE J oY 1 TA # aaa uni
Who do you think you are?
" Who do you think you are? y ©
Barging into our Bandits Hill? . pe
Barging into our Bandits Hill?
h Barging into our Bandits Hill?
TESTE
: You arrogant spoilt brat.
You arrogant spoilt brat.
SE teach him a lesson.
J teach him a lesson.
ha 1 J
. Showme what got.
boss...
MI your thunder?
Pal your thunder?
Fighting a ¢hild is just embarrassing.
Fighting a child is just embarrassing.
Fightin child is just embarrassing. pL
— __YoIryou..
ee ews TT TT yle. vy
gine to mommy.
~ []
- All thatshakiWBJolted me awake. 2 GEEK
i j He took too much of that pills } :
, ang now he's Immune. - 2
If yadfinsist to stay you mig He
If you insist to stay you might get hurt.
JOU insist to stay yo oc
| was going to dodge to the right.
Sorry, | thought it was left.
. Sorry, | thought it was left.
So wea
Maybe | should cut in.
| AE $$ Maybelshouldcutin.
—y
e could use a few more years’ training.
Not so fast.
EF He was just teasing the demon. y =
Lk] ha Bt teasing the demon.
L. YEE boy likes to... IR
play dumb.
Fho you'regnessing with.
Now you know who you're messing with.
| Now you know who you're messing with.
| The pills have dissolved in the soup!
have dissolved in the soup!
Then I'sitink the soup.
MEA SAIN . ; AT IZ _Nli drink the soups oo.
BE $42 AndydlEetryingtostealoursoup? vie PB
This calls for a beating.
Na J
Calms Ji
— 48
. So gross. ee
Super Mighty Club Strike! , yw’
Super Mighty Club Strike!
N Super Mighty Club Strike! AN
- 1 told you he was pretending.
Ta  _ ad Thatdidn't count. cv. Emm
-
rs
VY =
ct ge
Why did you spit it all out?
Check TH} out!
4 EN Check this out! +
nny!
Wego nn Ctitghuch nfl
EF 7 BB AEE TGA Sr
OE AR BE  icantgiveyouthepill 000 YN
EY A WN $4 whatdowedonow? 0 hk
LS
4 You're not suggesti ve
You're not suggesting...
We can eat the JE.
tw = degans. Fo
[| - That's hoW Nezha defeat fate.
: Crate add dan ale
_—
E-A-SYPEASY
v
-. EASYPEASYR RS 2202022
E-A-S-YP-E-ASY! oer
EEL an t will change my twine
EE Aaa | will change my destiny.
| will change my destiny.
rn IY Ce
J eT
Or today's show.
| BB. yf 0000 MasterTayi.
}- | -f Save Nezha first.
1 don't believe this. |
Fake death?
I'l smash you!
ood thing Nezha got knocked out.
"You do suck!
T=
i Let me avenge you! } hn
Let me avenge you!
nvincible Whirlwind Punch!
InvincibleWhirlwind Punch!
= «SST 0F invincible Whirlwind Punch!
Tr _a
I
y 11 » >
Ld
BIOIIRRLRYY y — =
ONY VY AP ERUT
a ALVA
l=
arm the peaple here
ake theiiBack to Yu XEPHEER
BEY $0000" nobiggy EST
His look switches from tim&g8 3  ]
spirit Pearl, you know, Jp
not like normal peo J]
Be more careful next time,
oF J. Ta 8d We
\
NB ' UE UR
- zal
J a.
Who's this kid?
. Nezha, possibly.
Younger brother of Jinzha and Muzha.
He's the Spirit Pearl reincarnation appointed by the Supreme Lord.
He's the Spirit Pearl reincamation appointed by the Supreme Lord.
Not likely, huh?
Hunched back.
Hunched back. ’
Wobbly pace. he
Sinking brows and drooping eyes.
Disgusting face. bY
' Not to mention the dark eye circles.
TY Not to mention the dark eye circles.
oo] More like a ghost. -
what's the star sign tonight?
DY Six stars in alignment,
he once in a decade.
cein adecad
this Jade Podium can transmit sound and images across thousands of miles.
this Jade Podium can transmit sound and images
L thi
-— -
0 e Golden Immortals shall mee __
Tey RJT Golden immortals shall meet Sin. 2 pr
= - he Golden Immortals shall meet) - <
Maybe ) shouldn't he included.
Maybe | shouldn't he included.
| A psonlyamattesoftime.
No la, nola.
It's not appropriate at all.
I can't doit. really.
lcan'tdoit, really.
am mm $2 aK
bly welcome you back to your places.
Greetings, Brother Wuliang! m
Greetings, Brother Wuliang!
SY Alloy, TI oduce AP EI.
mie to introdu neve member
Be
He has fulfijjpn TNE master's expecldtio
He has fulfilled ghemaster's expectations
We are here to discuss the preparatior®
e are here to discuss the preparatior®
We are here to discuss the preparatiorf®
_8&  CH®ectisthe orthodox of Tao, UE
CS. {SESE isthe orthodoxofTao, 00 |
I P9%c're destined to win. zd
I a 4
so we're destined EXE
8 idwhereulJIM000 beasts gather BN TO OB
Fis wii Tudyand hall beasts gathel .
and creatures born of mucus and e
oY
>
and creatures OOH mucus and egg
Ad Wemustbecareful@9@
We must be careful.
Stréngthening our power
Strengthening our power
That's why | began g
Pp WY | inmortalitypills, $0 Ww. oo UN
’ i J a total of nine thousands. Fr
. a total of nine thousands.
could be allocated according to grades.
could be allocated according to grades. -
could be allocated according to grades. g
y could be allocated according to grades.
This will definitely boost d St sf ength.
THis wilt definitely hoost our strength.
This oll definitely
undred §
ETRE ehy had GEIGER himself to bull OY se, $8000
his contributions are to be praised.
TT des the Jie Sect] bh
Biting aganst®@e@
are there other evil forces plotting again
i Master rihang,
CC theDeminT Lys Y
nT Watelybesent® 0909000
WE pose n®breat.  9@Y
so, most Nc pose no threat. +
Co herd ception.
-
N Ftagons?
Didn't they surrénder to the Court of Heaven long a
CS Ded ey of
NIRS PEY AN]
pidn'tthey sullEo the Court of Heaven lor
theirsitfender™dgerely a facadd! ll
hibernating for a mom
pele aabelue the al for thon
ET 2 GR Haug lus sundne ge
ERO (inve helOuenDanPE © abyss M
Dhsters for thousands of years.
What's their crime da UE
' What's their crime” )
reat strength.
Jutloifi —
Pr a-Aaliil
_— —
Eh mm
ur pun ARIEL us and luge is KRIS
CC ourreputhuon tf Behteplis dnd just is
tack tl
yon ever ti
wv will anyone ever
» . I otivd fa
-. ra
Caan
fruBeliberatidfis necessary.  ¥
3 TOVERUY PD IEoted.
and ou don't have tobe!
Pathe
nthe me
Jinzha and
are disc ples of myself and Brothe: P
[4%
They have been cultivating here fffliany years away from home,
They have been cliltivating here forffiany years away from home,
never even fMNezha,
WB nevereven met Nezha,
8 heir younger brother. - *%
od f PWIA EAE
I Et SWIC
OMG!
What should | do?
Speaking of my look...
. Speaking of my look...
’ Will my first impression...
Really?
Though slovenly,
Though you have black eye circles,
piggy nose
you're truly incredibly great.
Thanks for the compliment.
You go meet my brothers for me.
Seriously?
How can | do this for you?
This reminded me of my two brothers.
You have brothers too?
Having two such wonderful brothers.
You're so lucky.
What were you talking about just now?
They said
they're sorry for not checking on you ali these years.
if your parents are well,
what hobbies you have,
and who your friends are.
They also said
that whatever problems you may have in the future,
go to them.
And remember, you have two brothers
who will always help and protect you.
Why are you...
It's just sand in my
dan my
are it s not th ether around’
ot the other uv
I said nothing.
OK. You are the boss here.
I've been violent and unruly since | was young,
making my parents worry all day.
1 know TER y risk everything meee
i knowphegnly risk everything .
And today,
my brothers were so kind to me.
Our families have sacrificed so much for us.
and I'm a demon.
{We're bothbuflens for our families
We're both burdens for our families. !
So what if we were
Immortal or demon, t make the choice
Immortal or demon, | make the choice.
we must win ourselves a place among the immortals
we must win ourselves a place among the imn
so our families won't have to
Yes!
Only by becoming immortals
I'm going to become an immortal!
Only with courage and diligence can great progress be made.
«+ Only with courage and diligence can great progress be made.
Only with courage antfdiligence can great progress be made.
SS - . T Only with courage and diligence can great progress be made.
hundred years would still be in vain.
j hundred years would still be in vain.
IR § hundred years would still be in vain.
About cultivating,
the priorities are vitality, energy, and spirit.
If feeling hard,
Id
Sy ®™oted, ar 2
it's because you were born demons.
. it's because you were born demons.
A  y it's because you were born demons.
" . it's because you were born demons.
| SIGE by giving it your all . ai
by giving it your all
hance to change yo
you will have athance to change your destiny
and achieve immortality.
Life or death, of none I'm scared, +» el ~ a
Life or death, of none I'm scared, a dal h a
Life or death, of none I'm scared, ° B y° ~
defying authority is what I've revered. F 3 alll
defying authority is what I've revered. NY © A
defying authority is what I've revered.
My fate is mine, not heaven's plan. vl R aly. Soa
My fate is mine, not heaven's plan. ’ dae :
My fate is mine, not heaven's plan. ’ dated”
This bad boy will become a godly man! LAY ow
This bad boy will become a godly man
This bad boy will become a go d yan}
Bravo!
\L Baw  -.-.
Just a few lines, yet so powerful,
BRPuly inspiring. >.’
. " Thisis something ali of you should learn from.
SS . i is is something all of you should learn from.
= . This is something all of you should learn from.
2 Really? 4 + AY EE
+ Is it that good? a NN” .
I just made it up. Lew Fr Tv
yg
CC Tr ©
EE 1 ER
A poem like this
lA poem like this i
CC upad FY “ad ambition of you, young man.
YY a BL ambition of you, young man.
# ambition of you, young man.
db Atrue young hero
ith a bright future ahead! }
Lo a bright future ahead!’
7) Oh, come on. It's just fine. Eade oo A
Actually, it still has some tiny flaws.
More like plenty of fas. po
Ah Actmeaskyo Gp
J 4
a it's obvious you stay up late all the time.
Your life is undisciplined,
your diet unhealthy,
and you can't even manage bd
and you can’t even rffgibge basic self-control.
ow dife you dream of becoming an immortal?
AM | was born with dark eye circles. E
the heart, don't you know?
Y' WF VY Appearance re/S0eart, don't you know?
HEP at yourself in the mirror.
Ridiculous,
I.
reckless and sloppy.
I If you were my disciple,
yr I'd mdRe 0 rebuild your human form.
Fy = Rd snake you rebuild your human form.
y 4 Can be rebuilt?
Then there's hoff
| knew you camg tb Fil
CN | see you have great ambition,
CN Co so I'll take you as my disciple.
EE so I'll take you as my disciple.
CS ww Master
} train with your brothers.
train with your brothers.
a. WwW 7 Snortality, of course.
| don't need you to tes
Show me how to O0reriet?®@
Ridiculous
ting lo
You're putting loo
UE Get your prioTHIgRY aigh j
Are you teaching fhe or not?
Are you teaching me or not?
We're no longer master and disciple.
lL. 00 “We're no longer master and disciple.
tL “You deservegp have panda eyes for life.
LT 00 Ww You deserve to have panda eyes for life.
That's too much.
vas going to go easy on
I A Three pills should be enough.
iy for you.
Apologies. !
| underestimated you.
Yeah, teach this ignorant a
Te You saw it?
} We have no grudges between us.
We have no grudges between us.
You'd better go.
I]
: Lp even touch me.
Ed Speedy is junky.
Surrender?
You've figured it out finally.
I'm not fast.
| just transform into electric currents,
traveling instantly to any location.
»
1amMvincible!
| am invincible!
SJ
‘2 FAC ve fa
-
7 WN Stay calm.
| NX Bo hard and your body will collapse Willa ®
et's see what else
LB) fe Let's see what else you've got. « ) |
Lakes and seas...
I Clouds and sky...
wind is to rise and rain is to fall.
Swift and Uplift!
: Swift and Uplift! .
The Rain Summoning Spell.
oa ud Master, are you all right?
_— R——
pl Master, are you all right?
| wasn't going to take your life.
You didn't have to sacrifice an arm.
take the deni Stk to the palace. L
take the demEIHNCI:
Yedt
yd Nn FR 1 ye FT nee aA
CS al Putthemdown. 4
-  Allofyou,putthem®wn! ® ¢
May | ask if you are a member of the Chan Sect?
, May | ask if you are a member of the Chan S& Xk " .
Thatscorrect. WOK
These are all immortals from Yu Xu Palace.
You must not be diE¥es pectful.
You must not be di
Entering Yu
* Entering Yu Xu Palace
and receiving the teachings of the righteous path
- and receiving the teachings of the righteous path
-» may not be a bad thing.
may not be a bad thing.
All of you, drop your weapons!
&
2d 0 asl dl $$ Xiacbac? $0000 oad
AY 7 How colne you're back? hh aa
eR standdown! OY eT
's AEE TE EE BE CL. XA
So Ee you! :
freeze the river now!
There's no esd 3 »
There's no escape.
He's just trying to save his father.
‘ou didn't have to be so brutal.
Yeu didn't h
SW Hmph. Tm
Panax notoginseng, ha
cattail pollen,
borneol, -
dragon's blood.
One more basket.
Safflower,
angelica,
pseudo-ginseng powder, —
pseudo-ginseng powder,
poison nut.
gen My lord,
we now have everything onthe list,
we now have everything on the list, «till
4 “along with a hundred baskets of sea products.
; = along with a hundred baskets of sea products.
along with a hundred baskets of sea products. '
We happen to be short on food supplies.
Master Shen, a moment, please.
We've prepared a meal.
id you honor us with your presen
Would you honor us with your presence?
ThankstolordLi'skindnesSk «a
ee Wy I'vebeentaRBinasasevant q = om
EE. I've been taken Il] as a servant.
SS I'vebeentakeninasasevant Gil. 8 4
but he has a good heart.
As long as he behaves,
there's no reason he can't have a future.
| wonder if the dishes suit your taste.
Try this liquor as well.
1 quit long ago. _
Cultivators must sup... suppress desires.
As the saying goes,
one must cut off urg®s to perfect the spirit.
one must cut off urgesto perfect the spirit.
one must cut off urgesto perfect the spirit. -
Another saying goes,
one must practice kindness to polish virtue.
Talking won't help. i
I've already re... reached the point of no return.
You can't hide forever.
The truth will come out one day.
If you continue to harm lives
making more mistakes,
even if you can deceive everyone,
you won't be able to fool yourself.
And you will not improve further on your cultivation,
the essence of which
f the essence of which
is doing good deeds
and walking the righteous path.
You know nothing
about cultivation.
Someone is here to see Master Shen.
Who did this to you?
They attacked.
one of his arm:
had one of hisair
His name is...
His name is
RI BE TT IPR
w
ell -
Ladin. a.
Crs final tes
Shi die”
Ty -
NESE FCAT WH
Mine happened!
Let's keep looking.
Keep looking.
| received an urgent report as soon as | ended seclusion.
Who could have committed such a horrendous cri
Rhorrendous crime?
according to Shieldos,
they were struck by a tremendous force
and lost consciousness.
When they woke up,
people of Chentang Pass had already been slaughtered.
’ people of Chentang Pass had already been slaughtered.
We haven't obtained the elixir yet.
Why would they do that?
any clue?
| was just thinking,
where did all this lava come from?
There are no volcanoes for hundreds of miles around.
There are no volcanoes for hundreds of
Thisis truly bizarre.
This is truly bizarre.
Everyone, come quick!
What demon is this?
What demon is this? :
CS Thisis.. TY -oxt®
“8H |eftbyadragon's claw.
Impossible!
The dragons are all in Eastern Sea,
The dragons are all in Eastern Sea, !
The dragons are all in Eastérn Seb,
guarding the Suppression Seal.
Not a single one could have left.
QueenAoRunofWestih RAGE = =
Queen Ao Run ofiNbste
called the shy...
Sky-Splitting Claw.
ou saving she used the Sky- Splitting Claw
Are you saying she used the Sky-Splitting Claw
to cross into Chentang Pass?
That explains the ia
That exgilns the lava. ¥
It must have been transporte ¥ om the purgatory remotely.
It must have been transported i
It must have been transported from the purgatory remotely.
But she's watched by the Dragon King of Eastern Sea.
It's impossible for her to cross over.
Then there's only one possibility Jeft.
Then there's only one possibility Jéft.
The thing | worried the most
N The thing | worried the most
EN happened.
happened.
The King of Eastern Sea has betrayed us?
This is too serious an accusation.
Are you heading to the Dragon Palace?
That's the direction of Skull Mountain.
That's the di oC ion of Skull Mountain.
The dragons slaughtered innocent OO NERP
committing this unforgivable atrocity.
No need to consult with fellow Golden immortals
No need to consult with fellow Golden Immortals.
No need to consult with fellow Golden Immortals. ¥
I'll strike first and explain later.
all the Demon Hunters.
"Summon all the Demon Hunters.
Nezha's parents were killed by demons.
We can't let anything happen to the child.
en to the child.
| know you're heartbroken right now, FT
| know you're heartbroken right g%¢
put can you please
calm down for a moment?
take me to the Dragon Palace first? y
I'll confront my father and master
Will that bring my parents back?
Will that bring my parentsback? \ . OG
Mirror mirror on the wall,
Mirror mirror on thpwall,
- who's the fairest within ten miles and more?
uM) ten miles and more?
EY And who is the fairest within a hundre ps?
And who is the fairest within a hundred " les?
dwho is the fairest within a fmdled mites?
It's you, my lady.
Cy it's you, my lady.
What about a thousand miles?
And ten thousand miles
It's you.
still you.
EG I J
Do you think I'm stupid?
Lie better, at least.
”
No, no.
I WES trying not to piss you off. a
You know what?
Telling the truth won't’ hake me mad.
Telling the truth won't hake me mad.
Seriously? — EE
I I, Lady Shi Ji, am indeed a stumning beauty,
1, Lady Shi Ji, am indeed a stunning beauty,
I, Lady Shi Ji, am indeed a stunning beauty,
hut I knows the
Go on and ask then.
Am | the fairest of them all?
Am | the fairest within ten thousand miles?
What abgut a thousand miles?
Ten miles?
Am | even the fairest on this mountain?
Screw you!
There isn't any other female in this mountain.
I'm female, too.
You promised you won't get mad.
You promised you won't get mad. ———
You are prettier than me?
Demon, show yourself!
Who are you calling demon?
It's Lady Shi Ji.
Have we even met?
! What the hell are you up to?
You will be exposed.
But of it.
kJ
You think you can defeat me?
You think you can defeat me? \L
The entire mountain is my body.
I'll see how you can destroy me.
If you use more force,
- J
stay out of it!
Already started!
I'm so scr 5
I'm so screwed.
Luckily there's some left.
I shall live to fight another day.
Just you wait.
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
& Oh my!
Reckless child.
You body has almost gone.
/ Are you trying to kill yourself?
What's that fire earlier?
What's that fire 2arlier?
Who... who said that?
Frost, flame, | taught him everything.
His powers are
a combination of ice and fire.
Is that possible?
Can't judge him by normal standards.
Which one of us is the teacher?
You think you know better than me?
| wobldn’t dare.
owever, -,
| did sense a strong presence
of demonic energy earlier _____ onal
of demonic energy earlier
About that...
Shi Ji must have released it.
What are you saying, fatty?
Whatareyou saying, fatty? »*f
of Was it you? Just tell me, was it?
a sai
Stop shaking.
I'm about to throw up!
=~ I'm about to throw up!
See? | told you.
-., . Nezha,
TT Qe ™ J, you've passed three levels. !
zal you've passed three levels.
Today,
A N\ ” will personally cast \ T=
Iwillpersonallysast SR. = dill
I've been through all of this Hi CL
I've been through all of thisp Lo
gnger than | remember.
Rs longer than | remember.
you're
aw 4
7/"
. This Yu Xu Treasure Vault
This Yu Xu Treasure Vault
: « This Yu Xu Treasure Vault
-~ Mauses all sorts of agic items.
houses all sorts of rare magic ite!
E{ifir Reparo.
You can only pick one.
v you need more time?
t you need more time?
A Elixir Reparo.
b>
BANE A 2 A 2 2 TE
BY) 7 7 1 TdWiem the Twelve about what the dragpn®
However, due to the great distance,
ny bio thaws ved dive 1G Che real @ ance.
Eee. Jd . ’ .
my brothers and sisters can't make it here sooner.
- ity),
hy 0) SET INR
py EIJI em » .
on the dragons.
I will you fight alongside me?
r4 A Let me go back to Chentang Pass first. . N - YVVY \ a
Ya AA Let me go back to Chentang Pass L R Co TEVY aa
Then we'll seek revenge on the. Drag
TTPO #  f Then we'll seek revenge on theDragon King. Y Y V § UOAREAAA SAL 2 .
Ig A en'we’ll seek revenge on the Drago ng. YUU N - ASA,
you'd be a great helf
you'd be a great hel} }
you'd be a great he
you'd be a great help
2» N  Ivepadback NN
everything | owed you.
When | get my body back,
t will go with you to the Dragon Palace, okay?
You know well what I'm going to do.
You being there will only make it harder.
You being there will only make it harder. J
Next time we meet,
Next time we meet, i
we're foes instead of friends.
Ugh...
yw wr «amaitis. =
Ww
No, you can't leave! re -
Your soul will scatter before you get to the Dragon Palace.
JOWEIT®C atter Before you get to the Dragon Palace. hl
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
A. || ON rr ew. Wr TT
——
Calm down, will you? « UE
_ pli won't change anything.
won't change anything.
Leave me alone.
Let me out!
No!
¥  ipromisedN&a 44009220 =
I'd save you no matter what. 5
I'd save you no matter what.
Pah! Pah!
Suffocating!
a4
Co 'mdmaf® Wauliang of the Chan Sect.
braf Muliang of the Chan Sect.
dowou admit your guilt?
50 you admit your guilt?
you've found out?
Ao Bing still alive?
r punishment you give
litt please
but please spare my son.
The Court of Heaven ordered your clan to suppress the sea monsters.
Instead, you colluded with them
» and slaughtered Chentang Pass.
and slaughtered Chentang Pass.
The dragons have committed an unforgivable crime.
The dragons have committed an unforgivable crite?
Today,
justice shall be done. _
a. justice shall be done.
I. justice shall be done.
Encompassed are the earth and the skies.
Unleash the power with boundless might.
Let the Tianyuan rise and stand tat
Let the Tianyuan rise and stand tall.
oo ] Reign supreme above ENTAIL
pe 3 | Re) u supreme above them all
Open Cauldron!
{
) What have you done to Chentang Pass?
i What have you done to Chentang Pass?
ster Shen's orders?
Shen Gongbao?!
Speaking of the emergency,
ou should focus on present.
you should focus on present.
we can't sit here and wait to die!
if 1 go into battle,
the Suppression Seal will...
the Suppvedtistthand will ..
Joining all our powers,
wecanholditfor longlough.
§ I've had enough!
- I've had enough!
EE Youwvretched demon!
This is an once-in-a-millennium chance for revenge
This is an once-in-a-millennium
millennium chance for revenge.
This is an once-in-a-millennium chance for revenge.
: | Break out of the purgatory!
oo] Break out of the purgatory!
of 4 Destroy the Dragon Palace!
Destroy the Dragon Palace! o
Soul Blade!
Ju foal):
EE ] Taste my sword!
Releasing demonic energy like this...
aren't you afraid of exposingfffir identity?
aren't you afraid of exposifig :
if you dared to harm Chentang Pass,
~~ itaoffdared to harm Chentang Pass,
#@ou dared to harm Chentang Pass,
| would smash your palace into PIECES!
| walld smash your palace into PIECES!
J would smash your palace into PIECES!
Tell me!
Is Ao Bing dead?
Move! Out of my way!
AY a” oJ
Do yo d death wish?
Do you hI 4 death wish?
ban take'it.
AREER CH § lye or die.
bof | live or die. h, =
BR you're dead!
Now is the time!
Look what you've done!
Is annihilation for all really what you want?
is annihilation for all really what you wae
Even the Eastern Sea Dragon King can't match your power.
You're exactly what the Chan Sect needs.
You're exactly whit the Chan Sect needs.
parents spent their lives fighting evil.
you must carry on their legacy \
you must carry on their legacy
and eliminate all the demons.
FF Let me avenge your loss
~~ pytumnin@these bastards into pills.
by turning these Bastards into pills.
[FN Neha 0 a 4
y Neha BA Tw
Aa Neth2aoa A»
Son, are you alright?
- &  Yourbody..
Your body.
Theyalreadyknow ®
aboutyouandAoBing. @W
about you and Ao Bing.
I'd never see you again.
Master is still casting the spell.
We need to buy as much time as we can.
. it wasn't my father who slaughtered Chentang Pass.
it wasn't my father who slaughtered Chentang Pass.
The real culprit
is him, Shelreal eaigri¥uliang!
is him, the Immortal Wuliang!
ir'sbeenawhie. x" 009099000
it's been a while.
— vv
you collude with the dragons.
I should be ask... asking you.
| should be ask... asking you.
You captured my father.
What are you up to?
Who said | captuf pd your father?
Who sail Wptured your father?
Only you know my family's situation.
If you didn't give the order,
why would Nezha and the Demon Hunters hunt my father down?
y would Nezha and the Demon Hunters hunt my father down?
why wauld Nezha and the Demon Hunters hunt my father do
And my little brother's arrow wound...
It's obviously
caused by your disciple, Deero!
caused by your disciple, Deero! i»
There's thigh | recruited myself.
There's thé .] ent | recruited myself.
CC Therd'tRle eft | recfuited myself.
ME: fips past you.
Rn Slips past you.
So REBslips past you.
After all, I've done your dirty work for so many years.
I can also guess your purpose here
| can also guess your purpose here
You are trying to fram... frame the dragons, aren't you?
You are trying to fram... frame the dragons, aren't you? .
Is this how you repay me, your brother and mentor?
is this how you repay me, your broth
You've always use... used me for your benefit.
Between you and me,
there's only grudge, not gratitude.
May | interest you in a deal?
Master Immortal.
As the overseer of Yu Xu Palace,
spell to unhinge the Sea-Stabilizing
You... you are going to rebel?
A thousand years ago, the four of us fought the celestial realm together.
A thousand years ago, the four of us fought the celestial realm tog
Who's then betrayed us and
cast us into the purgatory?
0 - F- that's exactly what we want.
* that's eymctly what we want.
g heard that Immortal Wuliang recruit talents without bias.
I've long heard that Immortal Wuliang recruit talents without bias.
| trust it you know well what we can do.
I trust it you know well what we can do.
So ifyoudd
8 secret of the Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb.
Plus tie secret of the Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb.
Plus the secret of the Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb.
Whe... where's your spirit of fighting back?
We were young and ignorant!
A thousand years of imprisonment
has taught us about the rules
Smart.
= But you're so unpredictable.
T's But you're so unpredictable.
= How can | trust you? y
EE Unless you let me giice on you...
Unless you let me place on you...
We are willing. Yi
“- The three dragOWORwil WY agreed
lodet Wuliang place a curse on them
to let Wutiang place a curse on them. -
to let Wuliang place a curse on them.
If they dare to disobey in the future,
Wuliang can take their lives at any time. J
Wuliang can take their lives at any time.
Wuliang then fulfilled his promise,
freeing them from the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
ing them from the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
henever a powerful force is discover
Whenever a powerful force is discovered,
he orchestrates massacres,
and sends troops to capture them.
According to Shen Gongbao,
he had carried out many such tasks for Wufiang
he had carried out many such tasks for Wuliang
in exchange for a chance to join the Chan Sect.
Whiz. none Wd lap cane top at besten, @ neta Res,
mt! me the dlp an iL eotom ho
and! franee the d haps aff Ermem Sam.
ard! freon tthe dhaypore aff Exatm Seam.
One thing led to another,
he ended up recruiting the three dragon kings.
.. A y 1 d he learned the secret of the Demon Orb and the Spirit Pearl.
y ~ he learned the secret of the Demon Orb and the Spirit Pearl.
= a he learned the secret of the Demon Orb and the Spirit Pearl.
deliberately left two clueless survivors
they deliberately left two clueless survivors
to tell Yu Xu Palace what happened.
Seeing no hope of breaking through,
Shen Gongbao came up with a plan.
He had the Yaksha petrify us,
then hide us in the sewers.
Later, he waited for the right time to revive us.
My families are gone.
1 have nothing left to hold onto.
| have nothing left to hold onto.
The demons captured by the Demon Hunters
are not, as outsiders think,
being reformed in Yu Xu Palace.
Instead, they are thrown into the Tianyuan Cauldron by Wuliang,
refined into pills of immortality
to strengthen the Chan Sect's power.
how could you commit such atrocities?
How are you going to face our master
and the teachings we received?
linus acpl@p 01} Now that you kn8wW\itat Wuliang did,
Now that you know what Wuliang did,
CW “mwghoyld stop before it's too late.
’ : you should stop before it's too late.
Take him back to the palace
to face punishment from the Supreme Lord.
The Demon Huntl@$Wwere personally trained by Master Wuliang.
The Demon Hunters were personally trained by Master Wuliang.
Do you think a few words would turn us against him?
ou think a few words would turn us against him?
| was wrongabout the dragons.
| was wrong about the dragons.
Let them go!
_ Let me help.
You betrayed us?
We learned that from you, Big Brother.
Back then, in order to protect our kind,
Well, in order to protect myself now,
Neitherdo I.
Neitherdo |.
Don't leave us behind!
My King, take us with you!
My King! My King!
You've all been sold out!
Dragon King of Northern Sea.
Queen of Western Sea.
' it's playtime with your uncle.
Take my spear! b
So Takemyaxe! WHE |
Take my axel
- Take my wheel!
Take my wheel times a hundred!
Take my Wl tings a hundred!
Three hundreds!
There weren't that many.
Yourbodyisstillunstabieulle =
Don't exhaust yourself. Bl
4 4 Formymistakes,
i would give my life for freeing t
1 would give my life for freeing the dragons.
o> ung and vicious.
Let me have some fun with you, little one.
| Let me have some fun with you, little one.
shameless and vile!
A ae
- 48 A
How dare you hit your master's brother!
Bullying an uncle,
eat a knuckle!
A 4” YX EE WU
This won't do.
Then let's make it an even bigger one.
’ How about some vapor? ]
lr Ua '¥ Take them down] 9
ei A — am
Careful, it's me!
My apology.
Nezhal
LoL!
Transformation Spell?
) B Transformation Spell?
You can't fool me.
She sells seashells by the seashore.
You don’t know the code.
So you really are an imposter! ’ Ak =.
Unbelievable!
Serves you right.
Eh... he sells bells in the big well?
It's "she sells seashells by the seashore
it's "she sells seashells by the seashore
and the shells she sells all smell for sure”.
and the shells she sells all smell for sure”. oo
How come | don't know this code?
We just made it up!
Can you make it easier?
Don't come near me!
I'm the real Ao Shun!
Crap! You don't know the code!
Neither do you!
Does it mean I'm an imposter, too?
My goodness.
True fire of adhi Ignites the gold.
-— True fire of Samadhi ignites the gold.
Aperfect pill, its power@ffolds.
LENG
Swift and Uplift! Bs 3
Swift and Uplift!
\Why are you so scared?
Why are you so scared?
We uscd to bathe in lava like it's nothing.
We used to bathe in lava like it's nothing.
' ’ We used to bathe in lava like it’s nothing.
It's the true fire of Samadhi.
What are you looking at?
If anyone should eat this, it's me!
Yum.
Hyah!
BY wl id
What a Spirit Pearl!
Perfect match with the Demon Orb.
Perfect mate wn Orh
Ao Bing!
The Heart-Piercing Curse.
Dhue identities,
LonakulssLe
your true identities,
RENEE 3 nce | already knew your true identities,
Since | already knew your true identities, !
how could | not have a backup plan? ”
This is impossible!
That curse is quite complex.
That curse Is STE
That's why the Ascension Spell took so long.
I 4 That's why the Ascension Spell took so long.
Youslipped in sorflething. WW
Youslipped in something. ®I°®
aay Youodfar
Youoldfaortt ff - —
SS  - TTy
I
won't be able to break the Heart-Piercing Curse so quick.
won't be able to break the Heart-Piercing Curse so quick, J
won't be able to break the Heart-Piercing Curse so quic A
won't be able to break the Heart-Piercing Curse so quick. pp
won't be able to break the Heart-Piercing Curse so quick. pr
A thousand spikes have pitroed hp gh your nerves and veins.
A thousand spikes have pierte pugh your nerves and veins.
A thousand spikes have pierc@d through your nerves and veins. )
A thousand spikes have pierced tirougha/our nerves and veins.
Forcing any mivvement Fr
p71 7 7 will only r&ul€in your body | NLD
yy 22% ¥ begtomapad DN 00
se any living aura.
n't.sense any living aura.
ae i pte Sf
TSE. You were petrified.
Ss You were petrified.
ez
only fit
EE” The Spirit Pearl
I A and the Demon Orb
and the Demon Orb
are precious treasures.
I couldtreat you well
| could treat you well
AG | could treat you well
but now only for pill.
- but now only for pill. g
i : but now only for pill.
Ao Bing!
e still alive!
Ungh!
It's the Heart: Piercing Curse casted by Wuliang.
And he was ‘ g tered Chentang Pass framing it on the
And he was the one that slaughtered Chentang Pass framing ft on the dragons.
Father, -
Nezha was deceived.
Don't blame him.
Whatever you want to do, do it to me.
Leave my parents out of this.
Killing you won't change anything.
We're all doomed to die here.
We're all doomed to dic here.
If anyone still holds grudges,
the Chan Sect has a noble reputation,
how could you commit such a horrible clanger?
how could you commit suc
how could you commit su
Don't make more mistakes!
Why don't you go back and confess to Master?
I'll plead for mercy on your behalf. > 4
You...
iE riminate fooll
es ! place in the world is se
a —— you ungrateful slackers are half as a... Se
or you ungrateful slackers are half as hh, = may
oryou ungrateful slackers are half as le.
diligent as the demons,
So dN the demons,
I wouldn't have Bsted this much time and efforts!
I wouldn't have wasted this much time and efforts!
Even if it Sto My oWiiiOOR@®
Even if it leads to my own dot
Even if it leads to
I did it for the eternal dominance o
1 did it for the eternal dominance OF , an Sect.
1 did it for the eternal dominance of Chan Sect.
oo | did it for the eternal dominanc®®f ChanSect.
) conscience...
My conscienc@ftlear.
My conscience is clear.
Another one is done.
I can’t possibly eat a
i can't possibly eat any more.
You should try some. ~~
When my fins are done, you should try some too.
The claws are ready as well.
bd
The claws are ready aswel ¢ *
Weshould swopandshard.§ $6 .
We should swop and share. *
What's goingon? S$ & «
My body...
He's become a pill!
I'm still so young.
I don't want Lo die.
| don't want to die.
No, let me out.
EE - ‘ » JAE TT DE. &
DE a” - Stay calm!
-  ~ ly Focus all your epergy!
”, y 4 Focus all your energy! \
Hold on for as long as you can.
Sen!
arormne
You Can get through.
Youtan get through.
lkyou can hold out until t eart piercing curse fades.
Hop can hold out until the heart-piercing curse fades,
) you'll have a chance to escape.
you'll have a chance cape.
The heart-piercing curse takeSgat least six hours.
The heart-piercing curse takesat least six h
Iveon't be able to last shat long.
Ivon't be able to last ghat long.
Wake up, mom.
Nezha, Nezha?
I'm here, Mom.
You guys must not give up.
Don't worry about us.
{don't feel th
Nothing lalis yoo. kndda
AVY AF all> Nn" flamer, $000999OOW Em
If I am correct,
4 » If t am correct,
4 flames of the Demon Orb and the true fire of Samadhi
4 yl flares of the Demon Orb and the true fire of Samadhi
dé wy & . * nN flamps®f the Demon Orb and the true fire of Samadhi
4 ‘ share the same origin.
Then the Tianyuan Cauldron can’t
Then the Tianyuan Cauldron can't harm you.
Then the Tianyuan Cauldrontan't harm you.
Then the Tianyuan Cauldrongan't harm you.
BE 2 \ 8B 4
Bon't bother. | ”
EE This is just my avatar. A
As | suspected, the Demon Orb
is indestructible.
wonder the Supreme Lord had to destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven.
ofider the Supreme Lord had to destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven.
oo] Jer the Supreme Lord had to destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven.
The Oblivion Pill.
SS Jes. 030 Swallow
ard I'"f®ease your parents.
~amd 'lrelease your parents.
N What do you say?
4 TI moyBe ruthless,
di | may be ruthless,
but | always keep my promises.
EE but 1 always keep my promises.
but | always keep my pftinises.
Otherwise, all those elites of the demons
7 TA wouldn't swear loyalty to me.
DE wouldn't swear loyalty to me.
Al
| won't harm your parents.
Ivion't harm
What are you doing?
Using his parent?’ lives to threaten a kid? =
Using his parents’ lives to threaten a kid?
Using his parents' lives to threaten a kid?
And you call yourself a god?
You aren't even worthy to be a human.
Hold on until the heart-piercing curse is broken
. or your two brothers find you.
»™ or your two brothers find you. --~
fo fas
A vd can't kill the Demon OR. | yb
4. YBuredllythink) cah't kill the Demon Orb? WF yr
IR Est amatteroftime. Th WOEEERT8%0
I wm TE
yr Once you're dead,
| have a hundred ways to destroy him.
yr I have a hundred ways to destroy him.
WW Ihave ahundred ways to destroy him.
I have a hundred ways to destroy him.
I just don't want to die for nothing.
1 just don't want to die for nothing. *
" 1just don't want to die for nothing. }
I just don't want to die for nothing. -
’ Why won't you let me? ad
hy vion'
Why von!
Why won't you? -
If your trade your lifeforours, SH
ur life for
thin we could live in oeac
do you think we could live in peace?
No, mom.
This is thie
| just want to hug you one last time.
you'll have to walk your own path.
Useless.
| was born a demon,
and have always caused you pain.
| wanted so badly,
I'wanted so badly.
This is all my fault.
I'm sorry.
Evepgday | spent with you,
Everday | spent with you,
Everpday | spent with you,
Eves day | spent with you,
ml was so happy.
Al was so happy.
| never cared
~» | never cared
~ | never cared
—-—
1 never care
whether you were an immortal
whethg? you were an immortal
« orademon.
All Il know i$,
All) know is
All l know is_
you are my son.
will always
lov
Nezha, stay calm!
Your body will be torn
"SY JIT YY
The True Fire of Samadhi has compensated for
PR Itc omyrensated (oy
FIER Wl
Hh
firs
hil
Nezha's physical form
is complete now!
is complete now! py
take care of Mom.
Help me break the cauldron!
ee - Help me break the cauldron!
They are absorbing the energy of the Tianyuan Cauldron!
SS Roota Maxima!
Roota Maxima! a -
Demon Hunters, bygg? command,
BA
Ba entitihi
-r
” r
We've been backing,
We've been backing down
for far too long.
We thought if we gave everything,
then Wuliang would let us live.
But in the end, they still want us dead.
- ap But in the end, they still want us dead.
If that's what they want,
that's t they wont,
4 If that's what they want,
. then we'll fight them to death!
vr then we'll fight them to death!
B then we'll fight them to death!
Yes, let's fight!
ight Ficht! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
tle them aur
We can't let them
= ¥'&  Dponotgiveup!
Hang in there!
Jt
My cauldron!
a. foundation of Chan Sect!
Yc thefe 53M foundation of Chan Sect!
EE a 4 2
Kill all these bastards!
I You ungrateful traitors.
"EEG ungrateful traitors.
You ungrateful traitors.
Can't tell right from wrong!
I Roaring Dragon Waves!
» UE.
SEY. sothose two minions of ffs arflBnsters tS §¢ 200 |
EE -~it'¢all part of you
it's all part of your trickery!
You despicable lowlife.
How dare you oppose me! -
How dare you oppose me!
Witness my true powers!
one last chance because | value talents.
and I'll grant you immortality.
Hell with immortality!
Hellwithilly,
I'malldemon.g
Youclaimtobeaguldinglight, WPgpPF we ®
You claim to be a gui
You claim to be a guiding light,
but all you do is bully the weak,
and bring chaos to the world.
)
ignorant fools,
Ignorant fools,
the immortals rule the world.
Siding with the powerful is the only way out.
ro Siding with the powerful is the only way out.
! Either accept that or
| Either accept that or
’ you'll have no place to run to.
you'll Hive no place to run to.
If no place to go,
if no place to go,
if not accepted,
a EN | Meccepted 000
I will overturni
Iwill overturn!
My face...
- You fools broke my Ageless Spell!
You fools broke my Ageless Spell!
Nu old fart. a»
PRE $$ PW AFback tothe palSte.
‘ § Wait for me!
My father plans to ledIRITOR 5p
deep into the ocean to hide away.
Now that your identity is exposed,
why don't you ¢ome with us?
I've been hiding all my life,
until there was nowhere to run.
until there was no re torun.
Now I finally know how to face the world.
Now | finally know how to face the world.
Wuliang is one of the most powerful immortals
Wuliang is one of the most powerfufffnmortals ll
and is trusted by the SupremeYord. |
and is trusted by the Supreme Lord. |
He may not fall so easily. ll
He may not fall so easily. }
pf immipal@ei@demons walk difffrentpaths, 00 0202 umes
plus, imnMytals amd-demons walk different paths, B® 000 @z ‘Esc geaan
like water and fire.
Immortals. den
Immortals, demons
arc (Ler
ire just excuses for controlling those who are dificr
are just excuses for controlling those who are different.
= So what? |
now
7 hkyoucanchangethatl 0 o XT ee
7" ya youcanchangethatz § @00O0® 0020 TW aa
Ed
Pk yous can changethat? 8 BR 0 TF pane
Fvrant to try.
Perhaps I'm too old
Perhaps I'm too old i
to fight against the world. "
to fight against the world.
tofightagainsttheworld. A¢ ®% = =-w
to fight against the World. IN
I know that
once you've made up your mind,
you'll always follow through.
| put too much a burden on you,
never even
cared what you think.
apologize.
| apologize.
| only wanted to use my experience to give you a good life.
But now | see,
the experience of the older generation
and may not be right for you.
You mustwalk yy
You must walk your own path
u must walk your own pa
From now
From now on,
follow your heart.
| knew you'd come back.
Because we are both too young.
Too young to fear}
Too young to fear.
Too young to fea -»
Foun stage odQEADemw0¥
Is every victory worthy of praise faa LY
- Fen it all see world ablaze?
® RD) oC 0 it all set Maw orld ablaze?
[J Yom agoenX] all set I: N orld ablaze?
Can adesperileer BLL ddspair.
Cs OTT TUR ITT IB
Wi MD aaidh Bie divin 0
L
we /
ar
WiGHY dh Rive tive
GMs Ne tivo 1 Fran je: LEFT
Nothing fd
RITTER CEO CI TE TRNTIV TET YT TRC TET IH
vothing fafl
RIOTENT CEL CLV COTA ITCT LITRE IT TART ET 1
rv
me ween h
o RR ch cln co nica SIAR TL A A J
=
LE ad
-
Ld
A AU. my pT (OTs worth.
r-
DE | ZTTTINY yp LR (ITs orth.
-
IY |  ARARENTTIC Fic 11 pi LOO (LTRs v orth.
peg RR Be A
[hrough sandsostormeand thorny trails,
we .
Through sands, stormeandghorns trails,
Wyamgdi ALOR At TDR AO AIdny Sayit
Ton SLY RTI ED COLT 15)
(TUPI SEOXE aI) (Jaawitk
i rth ats JED GIO) PTawID
L TTLIORTT TITS LY 1 of SX A ABD COLT id
TTL RRTT OTITIS TT ri ¢f SE 11 EL LY
Rip pun: Tyra. adh wine
1'l
dn
(LIOR EIT] RANI Ch)
J 1
AER TE hi sha clicn orldisonichon .
y/ 9 ni Vis CHAU ORO LTR NIE [1 041)
V/ RID eno gifikgen 0 anti diam em
Vou and OE nT Eo Ie iD 41
Mouniai SE nT TNL] NTT EO I PITRE OF: - Pr a | ©
Let alRO OI CSTE TO OL [RICO
Petal RTC CSRS OJ OE0 TY
Tet [OH CR CRE Ti SEO Cl (Ie C0T YY
a eI OTE cc, ORE EC
ATI tepid is JIB) R30: 40 JEEP. wm ~~ ll
< og
PearSELAGRS Cl SELL ITY Tien dirs vp
rSELIUXS Co LSI FIENN uli STOR ITT INT TY
- In anin
UTTCTI IT'S CTT 1h I
2 -—.
ip In amine u ei au MTL RT
[YITTINN ITS 7 7 11 FO i LAT Td [ISS 1 Th 1
Yo Ih anaiaribage Vea asi ITY
Ju Mu gpswrdtibege Yeu gio D 1!
J WNC PNY. (ny icldincelgogind bring
4 te an ra aemegly en nai.
gu TOI Vea ately ein tai.
1 yn TRI Tea aOR tin nah